1
00:00:41,080 --> 00:00:42,350
Chow time!

2
00:00:42,510 --> 00:00:43,590
It's time!

3
00:00:43,480 --> 00:00:46,230
Dinner time.

4
00:00:50,080 --> 00:00:52,510
Only my friends call me Floyd.

5
00:00:52,530 --> 00:00:54,820
You ain't got no friends, Floyd.

6
00:00:56,240 --> 00:00:57,420
What's that?

7
00:00:57,440 --> 00:00:58,680
That is called loaf.

8
00:00:58,710 --> 00:00:59,300
A loaf!

9
00:00:59,720 --> 00:01:01,730
It's got a little bit of pasghetti in there.

10
00:01:01,960 --> 00:01:03,310
Toenails.

11
00:01:03,860 --> 00:01:04,970
Rat shit.

12
00:01:05,040 --> 00:01:07,030
Everything a growing fella needs, like you.

13
00:01:08,830 --> 00:01:11,680
- yeah

14
00:01:11,710 --> 00:01:13,650
One day ...

15
00:01:13,760 --> 00:01:16,550
I'm gonna get outta here.

16
00:01:16,540 --> 00:01:21,270
like the Holy Ghost.

17
00:01:22,900 --> 00:01:24,980
Man, you just threatened a staff number.

18
00:01:25,110 --> 00:01:25,900
Yeah?

19
00:01:25,900 --> 00:01:27,300
Yeah, you have.

20
00:01:27,250 --> 00:01:28,350
Do something.

21
00:01:28,890 --> 00:01:30,610
Let's have some fun.

22
00:01:59,390 --> 00:02:00,940
Open a goddamn gate!

23
00:02:01,070 --> 00:02:02,960
Come on guys. Don't waste my time.

24
00:02:03,040 --> 00:02:06,740
Boss is on deck!

25
00:02:10,020 --> 00:02:10,990
Open!

26
00:02:10,990 --> 00:02:13,590
Stay Back!

27
00:02:13,840 --> 00:02:16,120
If she moves, fire her up, all right?

28
00:02:17,350 --> 00:02:19,620
You gonna come down from there or what?

29
00:02:22,910 --> 00:02:24,050
Look at you.

30
00:02:26,670 --> 00:02:28,400
You know the rules, hotness.

31
00:02:28,430 --> 00:02:29,980
You gotta keep off these bars.

32
00:02:30,100 --> 00:02:32,810
- Yeah. Those bars.

33
00:02:32,820 --> 00:02:35,140
Oh, my good.

34
00:02:36,270 --> 00:02:39,540
You are really in bad shape upstairs, lady!

35
00:02:39,550 --> 00:02:41,450
Can you come in here and tell me that?

36
00:02:41,970 --> 00:02:43,970
or are you too scared?

37
00:02:43,980 --> 00:02:45,950
Come on, I'm bored.

38
00:02:45,960 --> 00:02:47,800
I'm bored, play with me.

39
00:02:47,810 --> 00:02:49,800
You put five of my guards in the hospital, honey.

40
00:02:49,960 --> 00:02:51,820
No one's gonna play with you.

41
00:02:52,060 --> 00:02:53,680
You sleep on the ground.

42
00:02:53,690 --> 00:02:57,760
I sleep where I want, when I want, with who I want.

43
00:02:59,760 --> 00:03:01,150
Oh man. I love you.

44
00:03:01,160 --> 00:03:02,230
Alpha one ...

45
00:03:02,380 --> 00:03:03,440
hit her

46
00:03:04,860 --> 00:03:08,500
She's a tiny little girl.

47
00:03:09,870 --> 00:03:11,810
What we got here?

48
00:03:11,940 --> 00:03:14,280
We got chocolate, strawberry or vanilla.

49
00:03:14,410 --> 00:03:17,750
Do you understand that?

50
00:03:19,080 --> 00:03:20,860
Spring break!

51
00:03:25,470 --> 00:03:29,560
That is just a whole lot of pretty in a whole lot of crazy.

52
00:03:49,910 --> 00:03:53,510
flew across the sky.

53
00:03:54,290 --> 00:03:56,480
And it changed again when he didn't.

54
00:03:58,160 --> 00:03:59,700
Remember.

55
00:04:07,020 --> 00:04:09,790
And that is why I'm here.

56
00:04:28,870 --> 00:04:31,160
Hello Amanda.

57
00:04:31,170 --> 00:04:32,930
We lose a national hero ...

58
00:04:33,070 --> 00:04:35,050
but you sit there looking like the cat that ate the canary.

59
00:04:35,390 --> 00:04:37,580
I've eaten a lot of canaries.

60
00:04:37,770 --> 00:04:39,760
It's taken some work.

61
00:04:39,770 --> 00:04:43,230
The worst of the worst.

62
00:04:44,750 --> 00:04:46,680
There's rumors, Amanda ...

63
00:04:47,370 --> 00:04:49,370
Some of them have abilities.

64
00:04:49,740 --> 00:04:51,010
The rumors are right.

65
00:04:51,470 --> 00:04:54,200
You know what a problem with a metahuman is?

66
00:04:54,210 --> 00:04:55,560
The human part.

67
00:04:55,920 --> 00:04:58,520
He shared our values.

68
00:04:58,900 --> 00:05:00,500
The next Superman might not.

69
00:05:00,900 --> 00:05:02,120
You're playing with fire, Amanda.

70
00:05:02,420 --> 00:05:04,080
I'm fighting fire with fire.

71
00:05:04,380 --> 00:05:08,380
You are not going to pitch us that Task Force X project of yours again, are you?

72
00:05:08,390 --> 00:05:09,790
Yes

73
00:05:10,280 --> 00:05:11,820
But this time, you're gonna listen.

74
00:05:13,460 --> 00:05:16,920
Floyd Lawton, AKA Deadshot.

75
00:05:32,150 --> 00:05:35,650
He is the most wanted hitman in the world.

76
00:05:39,400 --> 00:05:42,650
Let's say he has an elite clientele.

77
00:05:43,300 --> 00:05:45,670
- Hey Angelo.

78
00:05:45,910 --> 00:05:49,020
This is the exterminator you called for your rat problem.

79
00:05:49,150 --> 00:05:51,410
My account's looking a little thin.

80
00:05:51,830 --> 00:05:54,580
No one gets paid until what needs to get done, gets done.

81
00:05:54,720 --> 00:05:57,070
No money, No honey.

82
00:05:58,700 --> 00:06:01,320
Wow! Here is your boy right now.

83
00:06:01,900 --> 00:06:04,280
With about 20 of his new best friends.

84
00:06:08,860 --> 00:06:10,640
I'm still seeing zeroes over here, Angie.

85
00:06:10,780 --> 00:06:13,240
Listen. Stop being cute and do your job!

86
00:06:13,960 --> 00:06:15,850
They're taking him outta the car now.

87
00:06:15,970 --> 00:06:19,100
In about 30 seconds, your window is gonna close forever.

88
00:06:19,350 --> 00:06:21,360
Okay, Okay, Okay. Relax.

89
00:06:21,510 --> 00:06:22,930
There was an accounting error.

90
00:06:22,960 --> 00:06:24,090
We sent it.

91
00:06:25,070 --> 00:06:27,640
You got 10 seconds.

92
00:06:28,020 --> 00:06:31,630
- Did you threaten me?

93
00:06:31,730 --> 00:06:34,300
From all the singing he's about to do.

94
00:06:34,590 --> 00:06:36,490
You son of a bitch.

95
00:06:38,120 --> 00:06:40,070
Pleasure doing business with you, Angie.

96
00:06:58,300 --> 00:07:02,120
and a weakness can be leveraged.

97
00:07:02,280 --> 00:07:06,440
His daughter.

98
00:07:06,590 --> 00:07:08,890
So we watched her and waited.

99
00:07:09,030 --> 00:07:10,720
You should talk to Mama more.

100
00:07:11,700 --> 00:07:12,790
Yeah, yeah. I know

101
00:07:13,320 --> 00:07:14,770
Mama stays in bed a lot.

102
00:07:15,020 --> 00:07:17,090
Yeah. She's still going out at night?

103
00:07:17,220 --> 00:07:20,170
Dad, it's okay, I can take care of her.

104
00:07:21,570 --> 00:07:23,540
I know how to make pancakes now.

105
00:07:23,670 --> 00:07:25,340
Hey babe, That's beautiful.

106
00:07:25,920 --> 00:07:29,280
That's how that's supposed to work.

107
00:07:31,720 --> 00:07:33,460
I want you to come and live with me.

108
00:07:34,260 --> 00:07:37,960
All right? I came into some resources. I'mma get us spot.

109
00:07:38,110 --> 00:07:40,230
It's gonna be nice, all right?

110
00:07:40,440 --> 00:07:43,510
Mama says I can't live with you because you kill people.

111
00:07:43,920 --> 00:07:46,840
That's not true, That's a lie. She is lying to you.

112
00:07:47,100 --> 00:07:48,170
Daddy ...

113
00:07:48,320 --> 00:07:50,350
I know you do bad things.

114
00:07:51,010 --> 00:07:53,420
Don't worry. I still love you.

115
00:07:56,350 --> 00:07:57,970
Come on.

116
00:07:58,910 --> 00:07:59,830
And you caught him?

117
00:07:59,950 --> 00:08:01,000
Not me.

118
00:08:01,140 --> 00:08:04,210
I just gave an anonymous tip the right guy in the Gotham city.

119
00:08:04,570 --> 00:08:05,980
I'mma figure this out.

120
00:08:06,220 --> 00:08:07,880
All right?

121
00:08:11,800 --> 00:08:13,430
It's over, Headshot.

122
00:08:13,790 --> 00:08:16,540
in front of your daughter.

123
00:08:25,520 --> 00:08:28,090
- Zoe, move!

124
00:08:28,290 --> 00:08:30,950
Please daddy. Don't do it.

125
00:08:32,240 --> 00:08:34,080
Please.

126
00:08:35,060 --> 00:08:37,850
Don't do it.

127
00:08:48,340 --> 00:08:49,150
All right.

128
00:08:55,800 --> 00:08:58,920
Love you, daddy.

129
00:08:59,690 --> 00:09:01,720
So now we have the man who never misses.

130
00:09:01,870 --> 00:09:02,960
Where'd you put him?

131
00:09:03,090 --> 00:09:05,990
Let's just say. I put him in a hole and threw away the hole.

132
00:09:07,560 --> 00:09:09,290
Harley Quinn.

133
00:09:17,550 --> 00:09:19,330
Before she ran off and joined the circus ...

134
00:09:19,800 --> 00:09:22,160
She was known as Dr. Harleen Quinzel.

135
00:09:22,290 --> 00:09:24,510
A psychiatrist at Arkham Asylum.

136
00:09:25,050 --> 00:09:28,410
She was assigned to The Clown himself.

137
00:09:28,750 --> 00:09:31,180
Dr. Quinzel.

138
00:09:31,380 --> 00:09:33,980
You know, I lived for these moments with you.

139
00:09:34,440 --> 00:09:35,590
What do you get?

140
00:09:35,600 --> 00:09:36,910
I got you a kitty.

141
00:09:37,870 --> 00:09:38,970
So thoughtful.

142
00:09:39,120 --> 00:09:40,730
She thought she was curing him ...

143
00:09:40,860 --> 00:09:42,960
But, She was falling in love.

144
00:09:44,530 --> 00:09:46,280
for me ...

145
00:09:46,280 --> 00:09:47,300
Doctor

146
00:09:47,420 --> 00:09:48,640
Anything. I mean, yeah.

147
00:09:48,990 --> 00:09:52,760
I need a machine gun.

148
00:09:53,490 --> 00:09:55,250
A Machine gun?

149
00:09:56,940 --> 00:10:00,050
Talk about a workplace romance gone wrong.

150
00:10:11,560 --> 00:10:13,350
Get off me!

151
00:10:16,140 --> 00:10:19,430
What do we have here?

152
00:10:21,200 --> 00:10:23,250
You gonna kill me Mr.J?

153
00:10:23,510 --> 00:10:24,380
What?

154
00:10:26,970 --> 00:10:29,300
Oh, I'm not gonna kill ya

155
00:10:29,690 --> 00:10:31,990
I'm just gonna hurt ya ...

156
00:10:32,000 --> 00:10:35,770
really, really bad.

157
00:10:36,380 --> 00:10:37,660
You think so?

158
00:10:38,000 --> 00:10:40,060
Well, I can take it.

159
00:10:47,800 --> 00:10:50,580
They became the king and the queen of Gotham city.

160
00:10:51,130 --> 00:10:54,040
And god help anyone who disrespected the queen.

161
00:10:54,250 --> 00:10:57,430
- He ain't shake hands.

162
00:10:57,930 --> 00:11:00,570
But sit down and have a drink.

163
00:11:03,460 --> 00:11:05,110
Hey, J.

164
00:11:05,250 --> 00:11:08,450
On behalf of everybody, welcome back.

165
00:11:08,510 --> 00:11:11,270
personally say thank you.

166
00:11:11,410 --> 00:11:14,250
I'm making you good money.

167
00:11:14,260 --> 00:11:16,710
Are you sweet talkin' me?

168
00:11:19,550 --> 00:11:21,740
I love this guy.

169
00:11:22,070 --> 00:11:25,190
He's so intense!

170
00:11:29,440 --> 00:11:32,100
You're lucky man.

171
00:11:32,110 --> 00:11:34,500
You got a bad bitch.

172
00:11:36,810 --> 00:11:39,190
Oh, that she is.

173
00:11:39,610 --> 00:11:41,930
The fire in my loins.

174
00:11:42,130 --> 00:11:45,060
The itch in my pants.

175
00:11:45,070 --> 00:11:50,460
the infamous Harley Quinn!

176
00:11:59,950 --> 00:12:02,940
Oh, come to Daddy.

177
00:12:03,670 --> 00:12:04,810
Puddin''!

178
00:12:06,190 --> 00:12:11,720
Listen! You are my gift to this handsome hunka hunka!

179
00:12:11,730 --> 00:12:15,080
You belong to him now.

180
00:12:18,120 --> 00:12:20,780
You're cute!

181
00:12:20,790 --> 00:12:23,020
You want me?

182
00:12:23,030 --> 00:12:26,380
I'm all yours.

183
00:12:28,060 --> 00:12:29,570
I don't want no beef.

184
00:12:29,590 --> 00:12:31,860
You don't want ..

185
00:12:32,140 --> 00:12:34,310
You don't like me?

186
00:12:34,530 --> 00:12:36,120
Fine. Don't waste my time then.

187
00:12:36,130 --> 00:12:37,450
This is your lady.

188
00:12:37,700 --> 00:12:41,570
Look, are you enjoying yourself?

189
00:12:42,420 --> 00:12:43,490
No.

190
00:12:43,950 --> 00:12:46,500
- That's right!

191
00:12:46,840 --> 00:12:47,840
You, J!

192
00:12:51,320 --> 00:12:53,370
And, That was just the beginning.

193
00:13:01,720 --> 00:13:04,230
Come on, Puddin''. Do it!

194
00:13:05,200 --> 00:13:06,300
Oh ...

195
00:13:06,570 --> 00:13:11,160
- Batsy, Batsy, Batsy.

196
00:13:13,240 --> 00:13:15,050
She is crazier than him.

197
00:13:15,060 --> 00:13:16,830
And more fearless.

198
00:13:17,540 --> 00:13:20,380
Stupid Bat, You're ruining date night!

199
00:13:22,830 --> 00:13:23,890
Puddin''.

200
00:13:26,280 --> 00:13:29,630
Puddin'', I can't swimmmmm!

201
00:14:05,720 --> 00:14:07,410
And the Bat got her, too.

202
00:14:07,690 --> 00:14:10,660
She's in the same hole as Deadshot.

203
00:14:24,600 --> 00:14:26,110
And then there's the Aussie.

204
00:14:26,590 --> 00:14:27,690
Digger Harkness.

205
00:14:28,180 --> 00:14:31,620
Or as the tabloids call him : Capitan Boomerang.

206
00:14:39,850 --> 00:14:41,480
We're gonna be rich.

207
00:14:42,270 --> 00:14:44,990
Go and get the car.

208
00:14:45,060 --> 00:14:47,860
He robbed every bank in Australia.at least once.

209
00:14:48,000 --> 00:14:50,810
Then he came to America for a fresh target set.

210
00:14:53,140 --> 00:14:54,920
Doesn't work well with others.

211
00:15:00,000 --> 00:15:01,830
No honor among thieves, ha?

212
00:15:03,660 --> 00:15:06,920
lived to tell about it.

213
00:15:07,450 --> 00:15:10,640
And have you heard of the pyro kinetic homeboy?

214
00:15:14,490 --> 00:15:15,670
How'd you catch him?

215
00:15:16,000 --> 00:15:18,920
We did not. He surrendered.

216
00:15:19,320 --> 00:15:23,480
Chato Santana. On the street they call him El Diablo.

217
00:15:23,630 --> 00:15:26,430
he was the king of the world ...

218
00:15:26,550 --> 00:15:29,100
until he lost his queen.

219
00:15:30,870 --> 00:15:34,600
incinerates half the yard.

220
00:15:34,740 --> 00:15:36,890
The security video is incredible.

221
00:15:40,900 --> 00:15:42,160
Oh, Jesus.

222
00:15:41,120 --> 00:15:45,260
- His name is Waylon Jones.

223
00:15:45,460 --> 00:15:47,650
KC, dinner.

224
00:15:48,200 --> 00:15:49,280
Open it up, B.

225
00:15:49,550 --> 00:15:52,590
Evolution took a step backwards with this one.

226
00:15:53,200 --> 00:15:54,930
Give me that, Smitty.

227
00:15:55,810 --> 00:15:57,110
Where you at?

228
00:15:58,590 --> 00:16:00,530
They call him Killer Croc.

229
00:16:03,090 --> 00:16:04,610
He looked like a monster.

230
00:16:05,150 --> 00:16:07,120
So they treated him like a monster.

231
00:16:07,620 --> 00:16:10,700
Then he became a monster.

232
00:16:12,600 --> 00:16:14,770
He was chased out of Gotham by the bat.

233
00:16:14,890 --> 00:16:17,500
Went searching for sanctuary elsewhere.

234
00:16:17,610 --> 00:16:19,190
He never found it.

235
00:16:27,100 --> 00:16:29,490
I saved the best for last.

236
00:16:29,650 --> 00:16:31,850
- A witch?

237
00:16:31,950 --> 00:16:35,270
making- shit- disappear witch.

238
00:16:35,380 --> 00:16:38,450
Another world.

239
00:16:40,000 --> 00:16:43,000
Archaeologist doctor June Moone ...

240
00:16:44,250 --> 00:16:46,440
Wondered into the wrong cave.

241
00:16:54,630 --> 00:16:57,200
June ...

242
00:17:00,000 --> 00:17:02,310
She opened something she shouldn't have ...

243
00:17:13,100 --> 00:17:17,070
than any we've encountered.

244
00:17:17,600 --> 00:17:19,660
The Enchantress.

245
00:17:24,500 --> 00:17:27,200
She inhabits Dr.Moone's body now.

246
00:17:27,930 --> 00:17:29,750
Where is this witch?

247
00:17:29,460 --> 00:17:31,130
In my pocket.

248
00:17:31,340 --> 00:17:33,520
Now tell him why she won't turn you into a frog.

249
00:17:33,640 --> 00:17:36,270
a secret buried heart ...

250
00:17:36,510 --> 00:17:38,950
and whoever finds it, can control the witch.

251
00:17:39,150 --> 00:17:41,000
So we searched the cave where she turned up ...

252
00:17:41,060 --> 00:17:42,760
and we found her heart.

253
00:17:46,400 --> 00:17:47,590
That thing's her heart?

254
00:17:48,300 --> 00:17:50,110
She is vulnerable without it.

255
00:17:50,120 --> 00:17:52,520
You want to put our national security in the hands of ...

256
00:17:52,640 --> 00:17:55,910
witches, gangbangers, and crocodiles?

257
00:17:56,000 --> 00:17:58,750
- These are villains Amanda.

258
00:17:58,990 --> 00:18:00,840
What makes you think you can control them?

259
00:18:00,930 --> 00:18:04,110
against their own self- interests ...

260
00:18:04,250 --> 00:18:07,810
for the national security of the U.S is what I do for a living.

261
00:18:08,190 --> 00:18:12,140
this nation has ever produced ...

262
00:18:12,150 --> 00:18:13,640
Colonel Rick Flag.

263
00:18:36,700 --> 00:18:38,340
Help me.

264
00:18:38,470 --> 00:18:41,870
and just as I hoped ...

265
00:18:42,000 --> 00:18:43,670
it got personal.

266
00:18:43,790 --> 00:18:45,720
Are you gonna kiss me or not?

267
00:18:45,740 --> 00:18:47,360
I have the witch's heart.

268
00:18:47,490 --> 00:18:49,480
And Dr.Moone has his.

269
00:18:50,820 --> 00:18:53,710
Now he'll follow my orders as Holy Writ.

270
00:18:56,680 --> 00:18:58,760
In a world of flying men and monsters ...

271
00:18:58,890 --> 00:19:01,620
this is the only way to protect our country.

272
00:19:05,470 --> 00:19:11,100
rip off the roof of the White House ...

273
00:19:11,240 --> 00:19:14,220
and grab the president of the US right out of the Overall office?

274
00:19:14,830 --> 00:19:16,280
Who would've stopped him?

275
00:19:17,480 --> 00:19:20,670
for nukes in North Korea ...

276
00:19:20,700 --> 00:19:23,150
anthrax in our mail. We got fluoride in our water.

277
00:19:23,300 --> 00:19:26,250
the next Superman ...

278
00:19:26,480 --> 00:19:28,340
becomes a terrorist?

279
00:19:28,880 --> 00:19:31,320
Amanda?

280
00:19:31,320 --> 00:19:35,260
who I think can do some good.

281
00:19:35,400 --> 00:19:37,980
defeat the next Superman.

282
00:19:38,130 --> 00:19:39,530
Not on my watch.

283
00:19:39,660 --> 00:19:43,160
back out on the street in our name.

284
00:19:43,260 --> 00:19:47,200
Strictly need to know.

285
00:19:47,320 --> 00:19:50,000
we throw them under [???]

286
00:19:50,140 --> 00:19:54,540
with these meta humans. Ours or Theirs.

287
00:19:54,550 --> 00:19:57,120
We're not the only ones kicking up rocks looking for them.

288
00:19:57,120 --> 00:19:59,410
You know we can't control these people.

289
00:20:05,480 --> 00:20:07,430
June, Be strong!

290
00:20:07,920 --> 00:20:09,000
Dr.Moone.

291
00:20:34,230 --> 00:20:35,900
Enchantress

292
00:20:50,030 --> 00:20:52,110
Meet the Enchantress.

293
00:20:52,510 --> 00:20:55,370
is in your briefing packs.

294
00:20:55,510 --> 00:20:58,210
for a very long time ...

295
00:20:58,340 --> 00:21:00,660
when we're long gone.

296
00:21:00,720 --> 00:21:03,360
This meeting is ... is now a magic show?

297
00:21:03,600 --> 00:21:06,620
some pretty incredible things.

298
00:21:09,520 --> 00:21:10,920
Go get it, girl.

299
00:21:26,060 --> 00:21:30,520
the weapons ministry vault in Tehran?

300
00:21:39,390 --> 00:21:42,790
We've been chasing these plans for years.

301
00:21:44,510 --> 00:21:47,060
Please don't touch me.

302
00:21:47,200 --> 00:21:49,230
Thank you. We'd like Dr.Moone back.

303
00:21:49,250 --> 00:21:51,250
Enchantress.

304
00:22:01,700 --> 00:22:03,330
Please, Please.

305
00:22:03,460 --> 00:22:05,850
I can' ...

306
00:22:05,990 --> 00:22:07,540
Flag, get her out of here.

307
00:22:10,080 --> 00:22:11,300
I move to ...

308
00:22:11,860 --> 00:22:17,070
"Task Force X" under the Argus program.

309
00:22:19,110 --> 00:22:20,340
All right.

310
00:22:20,710 --> 00:22:22,980
Thank you Mr. Chairman.

311
00:22:34,410 --> 00:22:37,410
How you doing man?

312
00:22:37,680 --> 00:22:39,540
She is in charge.

313
00:22:39,860 --> 00:22:41,640
How are you?

314
00:22:41,850 --> 00:22:43,820
I'm here to assist you in anyway.

315
00:22:44,190 --> 00:22:45,710
Where are they?

316
00:23:03,380 --> 00:23:05,680
Are you the Devil?

317
00:23:07,590 --> 00:23:09,860
Maybe.

318
00:23:39,000 --> 00:23:40,920
Ain't you scared?

319
00:23:45,820 --> 00:23:48,210
Why'd they put you down here?

320
00:23:50,000 --> 00:23:51,520
I asked.

321
00:23:55,920 --> 00:23:57,360
You. ese

322
00:23:57,490 --> 00:23:59,380
Hola, amigo.

323
00:24:00,300 --> 00:24:03,240
You got visitors, man.

324
00:24:13,700 --> 00:24:16,680
What's up? Hey, you want some of this?

325
00:24:16,840 --> 00:24:18,130
Then come down here.

326
00:24:18,830 --> 00:24:20,480
That ain't me.

327
00:24:20,580 --> 00:24:21,580
That wasn't you?

328
00:24:21,760 --> 00:24:23,560
Nah, they say it's me, but that ain't me.

329
00:24:23,560 --> 00:24:24,890
That guy's gone.

330
00:24:25,080 --> 00:24:26,390
He's dead.

331
00:24:26,480 --> 00:24:27,920
And yet, here you are.

332
00:24:28,030 --> 00:24:28,580
Ma'am.

333
00:24:28,720 --> 00:24:30,050
Let me try to talk to him.

334
00:24:35,030 --> 00:24:36,980
You wanna die in here buddy?

335
00:24:37,110 --> 00:24:39,760
walking at the block again.

336
00:24:39,910 --> 00:24:42,710
Have a nice cold beer, a nice meal.

337
00:24:43,220 --> 00:24:44,030
A Women.

338
00:24:44,160 --> 00:24:45,250
Look, man ...

339
00:24:45,250 --> 00:24:48,070
and you ain't gonna be the last.

340
00:24:48,400 --> 00:24:49,600
Ask what?

341
00:24:49,800 --> 00:24:51,380
I'm a man. Okay?

342
00:24:51,660 --> 00:24:53,610
I ain't no weapon.

343
00:24:54,000 --> 00:24:56,760
I raise my fists again.

344
00:24:57,950 --> 00:25:00,080
I've caused enough harm.

345
00:25:09,320 --> 00:25:10,500
All right, unlock him.

346
00:25:10,790 --> 00:25:11,740
What?

347
00:25:11,860 --> 00:25:12,920
You heard me.

348
00:25:13,030 --> 00:25:14,200
You know what this man can do?

349
00:25:14,320 --> 00:25:17,570
Lose the restraints.

350
00:25:22,380 --> 00:25:23,820
OK.

351
00:25:24,700 --> 00:25:26,080
What is this?

352
00:25:26,470 --> 00:25:28,110
Cheerleading tryouts?

353
00:25:28,370 --> 00:25:30,210
Let's go. Let's see what you can do.

354
00:25:30,530 --> 00:25:32,220
They say you never missed a shot.

355
00:25:32,360 --> 00:25:33,590
Prove it.

356
00:25:46,530 --> 00:25:48,200
Now you got one in the chamber.

357
00:25:48,440 --> 00:25:49,980
What you gonna do with it?

358
00:25:51,210 --> 00:25:52,460
- Shit.

359
00:25:52,620 --> 00:25:54,280
I'll drop him.

360
00:25:54,280 --> 00:25:55,450
Everybody calm down.

361
00:25:55,700 --> 00:25:57,470
Griggs, tell your men to stand down.

362
00:25:57,470 --> 00:25:58,680
Tell them : "Put it down".

363
00:25:58,950 --> 00:25:59,170
Stand down.

364
00:25:59,900 --> 00:26:02,830
what I was concerned about.

365
00:26:02,920 --> 00:26:03,660
What's for dinner?

366
00:26:03,930 --> 00:26:05,670
Ames, if this man shoots me ...

367
00:26:05,810 --> 00:26:07,540
I want you to kill him ...

368
00:26:08,250 --> 00:26:10,170
And I want you to go and clear my browser history.

369
00:26:11,500 --> 00:26:12,560
See ...

370
00:26:13,370 --> 00:26:15,340
the firing pin is filed down, right?

371
00:26:15,340 --> 00:26:16,920
Mag full of dummy rounds.

372
00:26:17,060 --> 00:26:19,020
If I pull the trigger, nothing happens.

373
00:26:19,190 --> 00:26:20,630
You're absolutely right.

374
00:26:20,760 --> 00:26:23,510
to an infamous hitman?

375
00:26:23,660 --> 00:26:26,120
Go ahead, pull the trigger. Empty it.

376
00:26:26,230 --> 00:26:28,590
You don't even know this lady.

377
00:26:28,810 --> 00:26:30,600
I've known you, like, nine months.

378
00:26:30,710 --> 00:26:33,360
That was real cookie.

379
00:26:36,010 --> 00:26:37,420
What?

380
00:26:41,790 --> 00:26:43,630
Y'all Jokers must be crazy.

381
00:27:33,200 --> 00:27:34,930
Now you know what you're buyin'.

382
00:27:35,390 --> 00:27:36,960
Let me tell you the price. first ...

383
00:27:37,360 --> 00:27:38,660
I want outta here.

384
00:27:39,000 --> 00:27:41,980
Second, I want full custody of my daughter.

385
00:27:42,090 --> 00:27:44,050
And her mom can have, like ...

386
00:27:44,160 --> 00:27:47,170
supervised visits. But, her boyfriend can't come.

387
00:27:47,170 --> 00:27:48,680
Darnell can't come.

388
00:27:48,680 --> 00:27:50,310
- He's out.

389
00:27:50,560 --> 00:27:53,390
Third, y'all gonna pay for my daughter's whole education.

390
00:27:53,410 --> 00:27:56,140
And then I want her to go to college.

391
00:27:56,390 --> 00:27:57,950
Like Harvard. Or Yale.

392
00:27:58,160 --> 00:27:59,870
- Ivy league, yeah.

393
00:27:59,890 --> 00:28:01,390
One of them big joints, you know?

394
00:28:01,660 --> 00:28:03,480
And if she can't cut it ...

395
00:28:03,590 --> 00:28:07,320
white- people that thing. You know how y'all do.

396
00:28:07,400 --> 00:28:08,930
- You know, right? Ok.

397
00:28:09,080 --> 00:28:11,520
But I'm concerned ...

398
00:28:11,630 --> 00:28:13,560
nobody writing shit down.

399
00:28:13,830 --> 00:28:16,500
to make any demands.

400
00:28:16,580 --> 00:28:19,630
You thought I was talking to you.

401
00:28:20,090 --> 00:28:21,220
No, errand boy.

402
00:28:21,250 --> 00:28:23,260
I'm talking to your boss.

403
00:28:25,140 --> 00:28:26,690
That's my price, sweetie.

404
00:28:27,080 --> 00:28:28,410
You know what it is.

405
00:28:32,970 --> 00:28:34,150
You notice these are criminals?

406
00:28:35,030 --> 00:28:38,200
It makes no sense.

407
00:28:38,460 --> 00:28:40,300
and I'll build you ...

408
00:28:40,410 --> 00:28:42,180
anything you can dream up.

409
00:28:42,180 --> 00:28:44,530
Not these scumbags.

410
00:28:44,530 --> 00:28:47,220
In WW2, the US Navy made a deal with he mafia ...

411
00:28:47,350 --> 00:28:49,140
to protect its ships on the waterfront.

412
00:28:49,210 --> 00:28:50,440
This ain't WW2.

413
00:28:50,570 --> 00:28:52,210
It's WW3.

414
00:28:52,630 --> 00:28:54,050
What are you really up to?

415
00:28:54,420 --> 00:28:56,980
need to know is you work for me.

416
00:28:57,140 --> 00:28:58,760
That can change with a phone call.

417
00:28:58,950 --> 00:29:00,230
I have friends, too. You know.

418
00:29:02,750 --> 00:29:04,300
There you go. Call'em.

419
00:29:05,050 --> 00:29:07,200
her, your lady friend stays

420
00:29:07,330 --> 00:29:10,170
in a drug- induced coma.

421
00:29:11,510 --> 00:29:13,230
They warned me about you.

422
00:29:14,920 --> 00:29:17,250
I didn't believe the stories.

423
00:29:22,650 --> 00:29:24,300
Nobody does.

424
00:29:34,160 --> 00:29:35,520
Where is she?

425
00:29:35,670 --> 00:29:38,580
It's complex. This is not just her.

426
00:29:38,860 --> 00:29:40,420
Everybody's disappeared.

427
00:29:40,770 --> 00:29:43,040
where if you're a bad enough, bad guy

428
00:29:43,040 --> 00:29:44,560
they stamp "Terrorist" on your jacket.

429
00:29:44,670 --> 00:29:47,430
They send you to this swamp in Louisiana.

430
00:29:47,910 --> 00:29:49,130
A black site.

431
00:29:49,670 --> 00:29:51,040
That's where she is.

432
00:29:52,600 --> 00:29:54,050
So what are we doni'?

433
00:29:55,340 --> 00:29:57,120
bring the car around.

434
00:29:57,730 --> 00:29:59,940
We're going for a drive.

435
00:30:19,630 --> 00:30:22,180
Hit me one more time!

436
00:30:22,690 --> 00:30:24,290
Come on, Man

437
00:30:24,400 --> 00:30:27,200
to float me another 10k.

438
00:30:29,080 --> 00:30:31,220
- You know who I am?

439
00:30:36,380 --> 00:30:37,420
Good job, Man.

440
00:30:37,640 --> 00:30:38,650
He's killin' it.

441
00:30:38,690 --> 00:30:40,110
Come on Man. Why am I here?

442
00:30:40,220 --> 00:30:42,160
I get it! All right?

443
00:30:42,160 --> 00:30:45,280
Not my fault.

444
00:30:45,400 --> 00:30:46,260
All right?

445
00:30:46,510 --> 00:30:48,120
Dude, this is real.

446
00:30:48,370 --> 00:30:51,620
your house with your kids in it.

447
00:30:56,190 --> 00:30:57,520
But, you're lucky.

448
00:30:58,230 --> 00:31:00,250
Maybe. Why do you think so?

449
00:31:04,170 --> 00:31:06,160
You. Slick, what's up?

450
00:31:07,270 --> 00:31:09,090
Griggs. You are ...?

451
00:31:09,380 --> 00:31:11,110
You might wanna keep your mouth shut.

452
00:31:11,670 --> 00:31:12,530
Can I go, man?

453
00:31:12,580 --> 00:31:13,700
What the hell's going on, man?

454
00:31:14,020 --> 00:31:15,100
This is crazy.

455
00:31:20,950 --> 00:31:23,780
All of that chitchat's gonna get you hurt.

456
00:31:24,150 --> 00:31:25,050
My God!!!

457
00:31:45,340 --> 00:31:47,080
I could tell you meant that.

458
00:31:47,160 --> 00:31:48,240
Yeah.

459
00:31:51,520 --> 00:31:53,970
You're gonna be my friend.

460
00:32:10,050 --> 00:32:12,300
Enchantress.

461
00:32:23,320 --> 00:32:26,390
- June?

462
00:32:28,700 --> 00:32:31,040
- June?

463
00:32:31,240 --> 00:32:32,360
June?

464
00:32:33,260 --> 00:32:34,160
June.

465
00:32:35,700 --> 00:32:36,840
June.

466
00:32:39,450 --> 00:32:40,870
What did you do?

467
00:32:43,740 --> 00:32:44,680
OK.

468
00:33:14,000 --> 00:33:15,400
Sister.

469
00:33:16,500 --> 00:33:17,870
Brother.

470
00:33:21,800 --> 00:33:24,250
Pus, it could be the routing number.

471
00:33:25,060 --> 00:33:26,360
Wanna go for drinks?

472
00:33:38,150 --> 00:33:41,700
Brother I have freed you.

473
00:33:42,450 --> 00:33:44,410
Where are we?

474
00:33:45,090 --> 00:33:48,260
The same world only much later

475
00:33:50,010 --> 00:33:51,870
What happened?

476
00:33:52,990 --> 00:33:56,090
The humans turned against us

477
00:33:57,030 --> 00:33:59,690
But they worshipped us?

478
00:34:00,360 --> 00:34:02,730
We were gods to them

479
00:34:03,410 --> 00:34:06,190
Now they worship machines

480
00:34:06,830 --> 00:34:09,890
So I will build a machine

481
00:34:10,830 --> 00:34:13,930
That will destroy them all

482
00:34:14,670 --> 00:34:16,480
Build your strength

483
00:34:16,590 --> 00:34:17,770
Feed on them

484
00:34:17,860 --> 00:34:20,730
And wait for me to return.

485
00:34:23,410 --> 00:34:25,890
Enchantress.

486
00:34:28,140 --> 00:34:29,800
God damn it!

487
00:34:30,550 --> 00:34:33,190
June! June!

488
00:34:35,510 --> 00:34:37,090
June! I'm sorry.

489
00:34:47,870 --> 00:34:49,640
She went somewhere.

490
00:34:50,790 --> 00:34:53,860
If you have to choose between her or me ...

491
00:34:53,970 --> 00:34:55,550
stop her.

492
00:34:55,690 --> 00:34:57,810
Promise me you'll stop her.

493
00:35:01,640 --> 00:35:03,150
Even if it kills me.

494
00:35:29,910 --> 00:35:30,890
Sir!

495
00:35:31,020 --> 00:35:32,560
Sir, You okay?

496
00:35:32,680 --> 00:35:33,890
Can you breathe?

497
00:35:34,060 --> 00:35:35,790
Did you take anything?

498
00:35:36,480 --> 00:35:39,120
This is 21. Send medical to my location.

499
00:35:39,890 --> 00:35:41,000
I'm a physician.

500
00:35:41,150 --> 00:35:43,100
Roger. Bringing medical to your location.

501
00:35:43,220 --> 00:35:45,460
No pulse. Starting compressions.

502
00:36:12,950 --> 00:36:13,870
Sir

503
00:36:14,390 --> 00:36:15,700
Midway city is under attack.

504
00:36:15,760 --> 00:36:17,010
It's a non- human entity.

505
00:36:17,280 --> 00:36:18,860
I think you know what to do, sir.

506
00:36:18,990 --> 00:36:20,910
Activate Task Force X ...

507
00:36:20,990 --> 00:36:22,930
(ASAP = as soon as possible)

508
00:36:23,730 --> 00:36:24,440
Sir

509
00:36:26,430 --> 00:36:28,770
We're gonna live with Task Force X. Pull'em.

510
00:36:34,190 --> 00:36:36,050
Prisoners, get down on your knees. now!

511
00:36:36,150 --> 00:36:38,000
Turn around.

512
00:36:38,120 --> 00:36:38,840
Hands up high!

513
00:36:38,930 --> 00:36:40,520
Hey, I'm cooperating. All right?

514
00:36:40,660 --> 00:36:42,690
- Take her.

515
00:36:44,980 --> 00:36:46,840
Do not fire that goddamn weapon!

516
00:36:48,430 --> 00:36:49,580
Damn it!

517
00:36:51,490 --> 00:36:52,870
Open the gate!

518
00:36:53,030 --> 00:36:54,710
Everybody, line up for extraction.

519
00:36:54,840 --> 00:36:56,590
Let's go! Let's move, move!

520
00:36:57,250 --> 00:36:59,610
Yeah! Open the door! Let's go!

521
00:37:06,160 --> 00:37:07,080
Hit him!

522
00:37:07,200 --> 00:37:08,730
Hurry up, before he smokes us!

523
00:37:10,460 --> 00:37:11,190
Where you at?

524
00:37:18,310 --> 00:37:19,450
Is that the new guy?

525
00:37:24,210 --> 00:37:25,240
What is that?

526
00:37:25,580 --> 00:37:26,800
What is that?

527
00:37:26,950 --> 00:37:28,870
- Standby. Arming device.

528
00:37:28,980 --> 00:37:30,020
Who are you? I don't know who you are.

529
00:37:30,130 --> 00:37:30,890
Device armed.

530
00:37:30,890 --> 00:37:33,580
Hey ... I'm talking to you.

531
00:37:34,700 --> 00:37:35,620
injection Successful.

532
00:37:36,470 --> 00:37:37,770
Location verified.

533
00:37:38,550 --> 00:37:40,610
Anybody who touches me is dead.

534
00:37:40,920 --> 00:37:41,970
Anybody who ...

535
00:37:42,570 --> 00:37:43,570
lady.

536
00:37:43,570 --> 00:37:45,000
injection Successful.

537
00:37:45,120 --> 00:37:47,820
- Location verified.

538
00:37:47,930 --> 00:37:48,930
Next!

539
00:37:49,050 --> 00:37:51,410
Oh, you deaf. You one of them deaf hoes.

540
00:37:53,410 --> 00:37:54,550
Come on.

541
00:37:55,780 --> 00:37:57,100
Shut up, and get it done.

542
00:38:00,840 --> 00:38:02,480
I don't know where you're going.

543
00:38:02,590 --> 00:38:03,880
It's from Mr. J.

544
00:38:04,030 --> 00:38:05,520
You gonna tell him I took care of you?

545
00:38:05,820 --> 00:38:08,250
You're so screwed.

546
00:38:08,350 --> 00:38:10,160
What do you mean by that?

547
00:38:10,160 --> 00:38:11,320
Get off me! Get off me!

548
00:38:11,350 --> 00:38:12,760
Harley, what do you mean by that?

549
00:38:13,440 --> 00:38:14,970
Harley!!!

550
00:38:20,920 --> 00:38:23,930
I have a gift basket for Dr.Van Criss.

551
00:38:24,210 --> 00:38:27,060
I can't let you in. Sorry.

552
00:38:27,200 --> 00:38:30,550
I'm way behind today.

553
00:38:30,950 --> 00:38:32,840
Thank you. You're a good man.

554
00:38:45,570 --> 00:38:46,780
Open up.

555
00:38:55,350 --> 00:38:57,530
Just please, do whatever they say.

556
00:38:58,230 --> 00:39:00,820
Do whatever they say. Just do it.

557
00:39:11,340 --> 00:39:12,800
This look neat.

558
00:39:19,190 --> 00:39:21,230
Light it up! Light it up! Light it up!

559
00:39:30,560 --> 00:39:32,140
He's right above us.

560
00:39:32,320 --> 00:39:34,360
Rick, I can't do this.

561
00:39:34,360 --> 00:39:35,720
- Listen ... Listen

562
00:39:35,860 --> 00:39:37,400
There is no other way.

563
00:39:38,190 --> 00:39:39,680
Just get it done.

564
00:39:41,760 --> 00:39:43,420
Just get it done.

565
00:39:46,720 --> 00:39:48,230
Enchantress.

566
00:39:48,370 --> 00:39:50,350
What' going on down there?

567
00:39:51,930 --> 00:39:53,470
Amanda, she is bolted.

568
00:39:53,470 --> 00:39:54,920
Say it again?

569
00:39:55,050 --> 00:39:56,450
She is bolted.

570
00:39:57,030 --> 00:39:58,190
Shit!

571
00:40:02,760 --> 00:40:04,780
Brother help me.

572
00:40:06,240 --> 00:40:08,440
Before she kills me.

573
00:40:22,350 --> 00:40:24,200
Where's your heart?

574
00:40:24,520 --> 00:40:26,450
I will take it back.

575
00:40:27,000 --> 00:40:29,790
Untill then you will share your power.

576
00:40:30,380 --> 00:40:32,840
Now help me build my weapon.

577
00:40:33,340 --> 00:40:36,990
It's time to wipe them out.

578
00:40:59,860 --> 00:41:00,770
Go!

579
00:41:11,330 --> 00:41:14,030
Our weapons are ineffective.

580
00:41:14,160 --> 00:41:15,880
I thought this was contained!

581
00:41:20,090 --> 00:41:22,960
Guys. I need all three of you follow me please.

582
00:41:24,920 --> 00:41:26,510
Anybody with blood.

583
00:41:31,990 --> 00:41:33,490
This is the worst day of my life.

584
00:41:34,990 --> 00:41:38,230
to a FEMA representative.

585
00:41:39,960 --> 00:41:41,700
What's going on in that city?

586
00:41:42,250 --> 00:41:43,760
Those assholes here yet?

587
00:41:44,440 --> 00:41:46,000
Yeah. They're here.

588
00:41:47,320 --> 00:41:49,870
Alpha, Bravo team, on me.

589
00:41:52,780 --> 00:41:54,710
What the hell, Flag?

590
00:41:57,150 --> 00:41:58,290
Unlock'em.

591
00:42:06,540 --> 00:42:08,950
Hi, boys! Harley Quinn.

592
00:42:09,230 --> 00:42:10,490
How do you do?

593
00:42:16,690 --> 00:42:17,420
Haaah?

594
00:42:18,030 --> 00:42:19,020
What was that?

595
00:42:19,140 --> 00:42:21,280
I should kill everyone and escape?

596
00:42:22,920 --> 00:42:25,900
Sorry. The voices.

597
00:42:27,440 --> 00:42:29,890
I'm kidding. jeez!

598
00:42:30,170 --> 00:42:32,130
That's not what they really said.

599
00:42:32,400 --> 00:42:33,860
What do we got here?

600
00:42:33,860 --> 00:42:36,760
12 pounds of shit in a 10- pound sack.

601
00:42:42,440 --> 00:42:44,340
Welcome to party, Capitan Boomerang.

602
00:42:48,150 --> 00:42:50,670
Hey, hey, hey ... What's going on, man?

603
00:42:50,800 --> 00:42:51,950
Calm down.

604
00:42:52,100 --> 00:42:54,210
Hey, one minute I'm playing Mahjong with me nanna ...

605
00:42:54,360 --> 00:42:56,540
then this red streak hits me outta nowhere.

606
00:42:56,670 --> 00:42:59,180
Shut up! You were caught robbing a diamond exchange.

607
00:42:59,320 --> 00:43:00,650
I was not.

608
00:43:02,500 --> 00:43:03,600
Here comes Slipknot ...

609
00:43:03,640 --> 00:43:06,520
the man who climb anything. Wonderful.

610
00:43:06,670 --> 00:43:08,300
Have a good time, scumbag.

611
00:43:10,610 --> 00:43:11,850
Straighten up!

612
00:43:14,130 --> 00:43:15,580
She had a mouth.

613
00:43:17,120 --> 00:43:17,840
Listen up!

614
00:43:18,480 --> 00:43:19,920
In your necks ...

615
00:43:20,820 --> 00:43:23,940
it's a nanite explosive.

616
00:43:24,260 --> 00:43:25,530
as the size of a rice grain ...

617
00:43:25,780 --> 00:43:27,690
but it's powerful as a hand grenade.

618
00:43:28,460 --> 00:43:31,060
You disobey me, you die.

619
00:43:32,650 --> 00:43:35,200
You try to escape, you die.

620
00:43:35,420 --> 00:43:39,790
You otherwise irritate or vex me, and guess what?

621
00:43:40,520 --> 00:43:41,460
You die.

622
00:43:41,790 --> 00:43:44,840
I'm just forewarning you.

623
00:43:44,930 --> 00:43:46,160
Lady, shut up!

624
00:43:47,190 --> 00:43:48,350
This is the deal.

625
00:43:49,270 --> 00:43:51,500
You're going somewhere very bad ...

626
00:43:52,030 --> 00:43:53,860
to do something that'll get you killed.

627
00:43:54,000 --> 00:43:55,400
But until that happens ...

628
00:43:56,740 --> 00:43:58,180
you're my problem.

629
00:43:59,740 --> 00:44:02,090
So was that like a pep talk?

630
00:44:02,200 --> 00:44:03,610
Yeah. That was a pep talk.

631
00:44:03,730 --> 00:44:05,530
There's your shit.

632
00:44:05,660 --> 00:44:08,090
We're wheels up in 10.

633
00:44:08,220 --> 00:44:10,590
your team motivation thing.

634
00:44:10,600 --> 00:44:12,080
- Yeah.

635
00:44:12,190 --> 00:44:14,440
He's like a gold standard. OK?

636
00:44:14,440 --> 00:44:17,150
(Kind of strategy for effective attacking in basketball)

637
00:45:19,870 --> 00:45:20,930
What?

638
00:45:27,660 --> 00:45:28,890
Won't fit anymore?

639
00:45:30,360 --> 00:45:32,080
Too much junk in the trunk?

640
00:45:32,200 --> 00:45:36,200
Nah. Every time I put this on, somebody dies.

641
00:45:37,450 --> 00:45:38,350
And?

642
00:45:39,360 --> 00:45:40,990
I like putting it on.

643
00:45:41,800 --> 00:45:42,900
Goody.

644
00:45:43,150 --> 00:45:46,370
people are about to die.

645
00:45:46,500 --> 00:45:47,810
Yeah. It's us.

646
00:45:47,950 --> 00:45:49,360
We're being led to our deaths.

647
00:45:49,470 --> 00:45:50,700
Speak for yourself mate.

648
00:45:51,090 --> 00:45:53,240
Does it wash off?

649
00:45:54,780 --> 00:45:57,870
light her cigarette with your pinkie?

650
00:45:57,920 --> 00:45:59,570
because that would be real classy.

651
00:45:59,710 --> 00:46:02,230
Hey, y'all might wanna leave old boy alone.

652
00:46:02,380 --> 00:46:04,510
He could torch this whole joint.

653
00:46:04,840 --> 00:46:05,800
Ain't right, ese?

654
00:46:06,080 --> 00:46:08,350
Ain't got nothing to worry about from me.

655
00:46:08,470 --> 00:46:09,890
I'm cool, homie.

656
00:46:10,010 --> 00:46:12,090
Behold the voice of god.

657
00:46:14,910 --> 00:46:16,750
don't know me officially ...

658
00:46:16,850 --> 00:46:18,600
My Name is Amanda Waller.

659
00:46:19,880 --> 00:46:22,830
There's an active terrorist event in Midway City.

660
00:46:23,030 --> 00:46:27,530
rescue HVT- 1 and get them to safety.

661
00:46:27,790 --> 00:46:28,940
I'm sorry.

662
00:46:29,820 --> 00:46:33,550
what is HVT- 1?

663
00:46:33,690 --> 00:46:35,720
The only person that matters in the city ...

664
00:46:35,720 --> 00:46:37,670
the one person you can't kill.

665
00:46:38,460 --> 00:46:41,340
time off your prison sentence.

666
00:46:41,340 --> 00:46:43,190
Fail the mission, you die.

667
00:46:43,320 --> 00:46:45,060
Anything happens to Colonel Flag ...

668
00:46:45,210 --> 00:46:46,900
I'll kill every single one of you.

669
00:46:48,100 --> 00:46:49,680
Remember, I'm watching.

670
00:46:51,200 --> 00:46:52,550
I see everything.

671
00:46:55,560 --> 00:46:57,170
There's your pep talk.

672
00:46:57,430 --> 00:46:59,670
Compared to your shit, she killed it.

673
00:47:00,320 --> 00:47:01,610
So that's it?

674
00:47:01,730 --> 00:47:04,670
What, we some kind of Suicide Squad?

675
00:47:04,760 --> 00:47:07,050
I'll notify your next of kin.

676
00:47:08,890 --> 00:47:10,910
Alpha, Bravo team, Mount up!

677
00:47:16,740 --> 00:47:17,830
Your' late.

678
00:47:18,240 --> 00:47:19,300
I was busy.

679
00:47:30,640 --> 00:47:32,310
Please have mercy.

680
00:47:32,890 --> 00:47:34,640
Where was the mercy for my husband?

681
00:47:34,770 --> 00:47:36,740
I didn't kill him.

682
00:47:37,280 --> 00:47:38,840
But you watched.

683
00:47:39,580 --> 00:47:41,750
Criminals deserve no mercy.

684
00:47:44,670 --> 00:47:45,840
This is Katana.

685
00:47:45,970 --> 00:47:47,150
She's got my back.

686
00:47:47,150 --> 00:47:50,360
with one sword stroke ...

687
00:47:50,360 --> 00:47:52,650
Just like mowing the lawn.

688
00:47:52,790 --> 00:47:55,010
I would advise not getting killed by her.

689
00:47:55,170 --> 00:47:58,300
Her sword traps the souls of its victims.

690
00:47:59,000 --> 00:48:01,380
Nice to meet ya.

691
00:48:01,520 --> 00:48:03,190
Love your perfume.

692
00:48:03,310 --> 00:48:05,320
What is that? The stench of death?

693
00:48:07,750 --> 00:48:09,560
- Easy cowgirl.

694
00:48:09,700 --> 00:48:12,020
Have a seat..

695
00:48:12,360 --> 00:48:13,950
She seems nice.

696
00:48:26,560 --> 00:48:29,780
I'm coming for you.

697
00:48:48,840 --> 00:48:50,470
Look at that pretty lights!

698
00:48:51,500 --> 00:48:53,310
Are you guys seein' this?

699
00:48:55,050 --> 00:48:55,970
What happened?

700
00:48:57,860 --> 00:48:59,400
Terror attack.

701
00:48:59,660 --> 00:49:03,040
shooting up the place with AKs.

702
00:49:03,110 --> 00:49:05,000
You know, usual shit.

703
00:49:05,100 --> 00:49:06,100
Right.

704
00:49:07,050 --> 00:49:08,870
Yeah, you're a bad liar.

705
00:49:10,010 --> 00:49:11,120
I don't know if they told you ...

706
00:49:11,250 --> 00:49:14,420
I don't save people.

707
00:49:14,510 --> 00:49:16,020
Anything for a dollar, right?

708
00:49:16,590 --> 00:49:19,340
Don't act like you don't.

709
00:49:19,430 --> 00:49:21,150
I'm a soldier!

710
00:49:21,590 --> 00:49:24,430
who takes credit cards.

711
00:49:24,560 --> 00:49:25,920
When the shooting starts ...

712
00:49:25,920 --> 00:49:29,440
you'll cut and run.

713
00:49:43,720 --> 00:49:44,970
Six- one is going down.

714
00:49:44,980 --> 00:49:47,300
Six- one is going down hard.

715
00:50:01,330 --> 00:50:02,930
Stand by. Drop the ramp.

716
00:50:12,390 --> 00:50:13,760
What a ride!

717
00:50:14,100 --> 00:50:17,280
Assets are undamaged.

718
00:50:34,860 --> 00:50:35,850
Mind games.

719
00:50:35,850 --> 00:50:38,820
- All this bomb in the neck crap.

720
00:50:39,940 --> 00:50:41,050
That ain't real, mate

721
00:50:41,480 --> 00:50:44,120
with our own minds. right?

722
00:50:44,240 --> 00:50:47,340
But you look around, we're free, brah.

723
00:50:47,540 --> 00:50:48,730
How do you know this?

724
00:50:48,740 --> 00:50:50,910
It's a con.

725
00:50:50,810 --> 00:50:53,810
because I got a life to live.

726
00:50:54,340 --> 00:50:56,140
Question is, are you coming?

727
00:51:00,270 --> 00:51:02,370
Yeah! Smart!

728
00:51:24,300 --> 00:51:25,300
Hold your fire.

729
00:51:28,080 --> 00:51:29,520
Sorry. It's what I do.

730
00:51:41,280 --> 00:51:42,280
Damn it.

731
00:51:44,040 --> 00:51:45,640
Now that's a killer app!

732
00:51:46,390 --> 00:51:47,990
Okay. you wanna keep playing ...

733
00:51:48,000 --> 00:51:50,580
"I'll Blow your freaking Head Off?"

734
00:51:50,900 --> 00:51:51,990
Are you next?

735
00:51:52,730 --> 00:51:53,860
You tripping, homie.

736
00:51:54,910 --> 00:51:56,110
You next, Deadshot?

737
00:51:59,440 --> 00:52:00,440
You just threatened me?

738
00:52:00,890 --> 00:52:01,890
Oh, yeah.

739
00:52:02,760 --> 00:52:04,220
He just threatened me.

740
00:52:07,560 --> 00:52:08,810
Move.

741
00:52:09,290 --> 00:52:10,940
You got a boyfriend?

742
00:52:14,790 --> 00:52:16,060
I'm gonna kill him.

743
00:52:16,320 --> 00:52:19,570
'cause he's gonna kill all of us one by one.

744
00:52:19,960 --> 00:52:22,700
five or seven of these SEALs.

745
00:52:22,700 --> 00:52:24,560
you down?

746
00:52:24,740 --> 00:52:27,140
the shit in our necks?

747
00:52:27,570 --> 00:52:30,630
help us out with that, right?

748
00:52:33,500 --> 00:52:35,570
You're my friend, too.

749
00:52:36,890 --> 00:52:39,810
Stay evil, doll face, Spread the word.

750
00:52:43,180 --> 00:52:46,100
I'm standing by for follow on tasking.

751
00:52:56,320 --> 00:52:58,430
C2, what is the operational load of the PLS?

752
00:52:58,680 --> 00:53:00,300
Boss, we got people up here.

753
00:53:01,400 --> 00:53:02,700
I'm on my way.

754
00:53:15,420 --> 00:53:16,390
Shit!

755
00:53:16,600 --> 00:53:18,450
Amanda, we have hostiles up ahead.

756
00:53:18,570 --> 00:53:20,040
Flag. get out of there.

757
00:53:20,320 --> 00:53:22,710
We know that doesn't work.

758
00:53:22,910 --> 00:53:23,910
Copy that.

759
00:53:24,590 --> 00:53:25,910
We're diverting.

760
00:53:26,140 --> 00:53:28,670
Bump out second two squad two blocks east.

761
00:53:28,780 --> 00:53:29,980
We'll pass through you ...

762
00:53:30,230 --> 00:53:31,230
continue north.

763
00:53:31,650 --> 00:53:33,250
Take Bravo two blocks east.

764
00:53:33,250 --> 00:53:35,040
once you're in position.

765
00:53:35,040 --> 00:53:36,040
Copy that.

766
00:53:43,460 --> 00:53:46,600
Hey. I like these odds, mate.

767
00:53:46,790 --> 00:53:47,950
You just say the word.

768
00:53:48,080 --> 00:53:49,080
Yeah.

769
00:53:49,800 --> 00:53:50,800
Come on.

770
00:53:51,170 --> 00:53:52,170
Yeah.

771
00:53:52,670 --> 00:53:53,940
Hold  that thought.

772
00:54:03,220 --> 00:54:05,350
Rick, why do they look like that?

773
00:54:05,440 --> 00:54:06,440
Just stay cool.

774
00:54:19,160 --> 00:54:20,360
The hell are they?

775
00:54:21,100 --> 00:54:23,620
I'll blow your head off.

776
00:54:35,110 --> 00:54:36,110
Hit'em!

777
00:55:33,260 --> 00:55:34,120
Hey.

778
00:56:00,040 --> 00:56:01,040
Get off me!

779
00:56:05,120 --> 00:56:06,690
Get off me! Son of a ...

780
00:56:11,060 --> 00:56:12,060
Flag!

781
00:56:13,600 --> 00:56:14,770
- Harley

782
00:56:14,790 --> 00:56:15,790
He dies. we die.

783
00:56:28,590 --> 00:56:29,850
- Shut up.

784
00:56:32,260 --> 00:56:33,330
Backblast, clear!

785
00:57:22,350 --> 00:57:23,350
Pinky.

786
00:57:27,670 --> 00:57:30,040
That's how I cut and run.

787
00:57:37,600 --> 00:57:38,600
Hey.

788
00:57:39,080 --> 00:57:40,080
Hey. come on.

789
00:57:40,490 --> 00:57:42,250
What? I saw it move.

790
00:57:43,330 --> 00:57:45,950
I think.

791
00:57:46,910 --> 00:57:48,860
Hey. you were some help. princess.

792
00:57:49,350 --> 00:57:50,750
It's better this way.

793
00:57:51,200 --> 00:57:52,200
Trust me.

794
00:57:52,590 --> 00:57:54,450
Oh, yeah you're the fire bloke. eh?

795
00:57:54,460 --> 00:57:54,940
Yeah, I was. Yeah.

796
00:57:54,950 --> 00:57:56,610
Right. Yeah. Hey.

797
00:57:57,820 --> 00:57:58,890
Well. look at here.

798
00:57:59,530 --> 00:58:00,530
It's fire.

799
00:58:09,090 --> 00:58:10,300
Wants to explain this?

800
00:58:10,290 --> 00:58:11,860
If I told you, would you believe me?

801
00:58:13,540 --> 00:58:15,280
- I don't know.

802
00:58:15,360 --> 00:58:16,700
That's bullshit.

803
00:58:17,220 --> 00:58:19,730
This guy had a 3000$ watch.

804
00:58:21,090 --> 00:58:22,440
Is that a Person?

805
00:58:23,160 --> 00:58:24,450
It was.

806
00:58:25,080 --> 00:58:26,280
Now it's not.

807
00:58:27,630 --> 00:58:28,990
Hey, don't.

808
00:58:29,290 --> 00:58:30,630
What?

809
00:58:30,890 --> 00:58:32,490
We got a job to do.

810
00:58:35,330 --> 00:58:36,350
Keep movin'.

811
00:58:39,270 --> 00:58:41,080
Get your boys moving.

812
00:58:43,750 --> 00:58:45,080
Let's go.

813
00:58:53,990 --> 00:58:55,600
Waller, we are moving toward the objective.

814
00:58:55,730 --> 00:58:57,760
... Contacting Bravo. you got the visual?

815
00:58:57,810 --> 00:58:58,600
Stand by.

816
00:58:58,750 --> 00:58:59,950
Anything on the squadron?

817
00:58:59,990 --> 00:59:00,840
No ma'am.

818
00:59:01,150 --> 00:59:03,680
in those coordinates.

819
00:59:03,760 --> 00:59:04,780
Flag, it's a negative.

820
00:59:04,930 --> 00:59:07,820
[???], but we've lost them.

821
00:59:44,790 --> 00:59:45,680
Seriously?

822
00:59:45,880 --> 00:59:47,760
What the hell is wrong with you people?

823
00:59:48,280 --> 00:59:51,930
It's what we do.

824
01:00:10,670 --> 01:00:11,670
Take a knee.

825
01:00:17,390 --> 01:00:19,170
Our body's at the top of that building.

826
01:00:19,870 --> 01:00:20,200
We get up there ...

827
01:00:20,450 --> 01:00:22,190
the vault they're hiding in.

828
01:00:22,200 --> 01:00:24,280
Helos extract us off the roof.

829
01:00:24,290 --> 01:00:26,070
- Check

830
01:00:38,970 --> 01:00:39,780
Waller?

831
01:00:40,550 --> 01:00:43,430
Get that chopper ready.

832
01:00:47,690 --> 01:00:49,090
What do say we get this over with?

833
01:00:49,130 --> 01:00:50,520
What the hell? Deadshot.

834
01:00:50,630 --> 01:00:51,910
Fall back.

835
01:00:57,700 --> 01:00:59,530
You mind if we tag along?

836
01:01:13,190 --> 01:01:15,130
look like we have a spot of luck.eh?

837
01:01:16,040 --> 01:01:17,790
Be a walk in the park.

838
01:01:18,100 --> 01:01:19,570
Easy peasy.

839
01:01:19,670 --> 01:01:21,810
Don't make me shoot you.

840
01:01:26,960 --> 01:01:28,910
God damn it. Harley!

841
01:01:29,170 --> 01:01:30,520
Go! Go! Go! Go!

842
01:01:34,790 --> 01:01:37,110
I am coming to my lady ...

843
01:02:18,450 --> 01:02:19,280
Hey, guys!

844
01:02:26,200 --> 01:02:27,560
Come on. Let's go.

845
01:02:36,960 --> 01:02:40,640
going off on the secure floors.

846
01:02:43,040 --> 01:02:43,880
Flag...

847
01:02:44,010 --> 01:02:45,370
- Hold

848
01:02:45,450 --> 01:02:47,660
Use extreme caution.

849
01:02:58,690 --> 01:02:59,690
Pussy.

850
01:02:59,660 --> 01:03:01,610
I will knock your ass out.

851
01:03:01,960 --> 01:03:04,210
I do not care that you're a girl.

852
01:03:53,850 --> 01:03:55,210
They're after Flag again.

853
01:03:56,500 --> 01:03:57,950
Get off me.

854
01:04:02,490 --> 01:04:04,070
Circle up. Circle around him.

855
01:04:09,630 --> 01:04:10,630
Let me fight!

856
01:04:10,430 --> 01:04:12,020
You die. We die.

857
01:04:15,050 --> 01:04:17,030
Clear! Everyone move out.

858
01:04:33,270 --> 01:04:36,050
You ain't about shit!

859
01:04:36,160 --> 01:04:37,350
Don't touch me, man!

860
01:04:37,350 --> 01:04:38,620
- Don't touch me!

861
01:04:42,720 --> 01:04:43,840
- Yes, I wanna see ...

862
01:04:44,000 --> 01:04:45,580
- Yes I wanna see something.

863
01:05:10,500 --> 01:05:12,390
I was just trying to get you there.

864
01:05:13,610 --> 01:05:15,240
Phil Jackson. We good, right?

865
01:05:17,480 --> 01:05:19,960
I knew you'd come through.

866
01:05:20,470 --> 01:05:22,040
That shit crazy.

867
01:05:31,870 --> 01:05:33,300
Clear.

868
01:05:46,630 --> 01:05:49,240
I gotta work on my cardio.

869
01:05:58,820 --> 01:05:59,820
Question.

870
01:06:02,700 --> 01:06:04,540
Would you die for me?

871
01:06:07,060 --> 01:06:07,650
Yes.

872
01:06:07,860 --> 01:06:09,470
That's too easy.

873
01:06:10,450 --> 01:06:12,110
Would you ... ?

874
01:06:14,350 --> 01:06:15,820
Would you live for me?

875
01:06:19,680 --> 01:06:20,680
Yes

876
01:06:21,680 --> 01:06:23,310
Careful.

877
01:06:23,370 --> 01:06:28,600
Do not say this oath thoughtlessly.

878
01:06:29,890 --> 01:06:30,680
Desire becomes surrender.

879
01:06:31,020 --> 01:06:33,520
Surrender becomes power.

880
01:06:37,110 --> 01:06:38,780
Do you want this?

881
01:06:39,760 --> 01:06:40,830
I do.

882
01:06:40,830 --> 01:06:42,380
say it.

883
01:06:42,530 --> 01:06:45,080
Say it. Say it.

884
01:06:45,220 --> 01:06:47,840
Pretty, pretty, pretty ...

885
01:06:48,010 --> 01:06:49,010
Please.

886
01:06:50,200 --> 01:06:52,040
God, you're so ...

887
01:06:52,550 --> 01:06:53,550
Good.

888
01:08:00,870 --> 01:08:01,760
Relax.

889
01:08:01,760 --> 01:08:02,760
Just me.

890
01:08:06,540 --> 01:08:08,710
You ever been in love?

891
01:08:10,710 --> 01:08:12,700
Nah. never.

892
01:08:12,710 --> 01:08:14,040
Bullshit.

893
01:08:14,220 --> 01:08:17,940
I've killed and still sleep like a kitten

894
01:08:18,070 --> 01:08:19,870
If you feel shit like love.

895
01:08:22,210 --> 01:08:24,440
Another textbook sociopath.

896
01:08:28,300 --> 01:08:29,300
Clear.

897
01:08:29,320 --> 01:08:30,610
Clear.

898
01:08:32,120 --> 01:08:33,050
All right, secure the roof.

899
01:08:33,060 --> 01:08:35,990
so we can bring in our aviation assets.

900
01:08:36,200 --> 01:08:37,300
Going to the roof.

901
01:08:45,000 --> 01:08:46,000
Wait here.

902
01:08:46,160 --> 01:08:47,160
Please.

903
01:08:47,360 --> 01:08:50,630
a heart attack okay?

904
01:08:50,980 --> 01:08:52,880
He's embarrassed of us.

905
01:08:52,910 --> 01:08:53,910
Hey, Flag.

906
01:08:54,520 --> 01:08:58,050
after all of this shit.

907
01:09:03,840 --> 01:09:06,700
You ready? let's go.

908
01:09:06,810 --> 01:09:09,050
You wouldn't have made it without them.

909
01:09:09,100 --> 01:09:12,080
I do planning and precision.

910
01:09:12,180 --> 01:09:14,740
Admit it, rick. I was right.

911
01:09:14,870 --> 01:09:16,530
Yeah, I told you to get on the damn truck.

912
01:09:16,610 --> 01:09:17,430
Why'd you say?

913
01:09:17,520 --> 01:09:19,470
I was studying your girlfriend.

914
01:09:19,610 --> 01:09:21,070
She takes an average person ...

915
01:09:21,210 --> 01:09:24,510
and she turns them into a soldier

916
01:09:24,510 --> 01:09:26,700
Who can take a headshot and still fight.

917
01:09:27,200 --> 01:09:28,830
It's an instant army.

918
01:09:29,630 --> 01:09:31,030
How'd she do it. Flag?

919
01:09:31,650 --> 01:09:32,850
How'd she game the system ...

920
01:09:32,850 --> 01:09:34,930
With you watching her every move?

921
01:09:37,960 --> 01:09:39,820
I'll accept the consequences

922
01:09:40,360 --> 01:09:41,930
I am your consequence.

923
01:09:41,970 --> 01:09:43,820
You might need to be careful.

924
01:09:44,250 --> 01:09:46,580
They think we're rescuing Nelson Mandela.

925
01:09:46,680 --> 01:09:48,210
I can take care of myself.

926
01:09:48,340 --> 01:09:50,230
- Yes, ma'am.

927
01:09:50,390 --> 01:09:51,620
Copy that.

928
01:09:52,340 --> 01:09:54,680
'cause you're trapped ...

929
01:09:54,720 --> 01:09:57,770
soldierly self- righteousness ...

930
01:09:57,930 --> 01:10:01,140
wouldn't survive a second on the street.

931
01:10:01,140 --> 01:10:03,150
Oh, says the guy who shoots people for money.

932
01:10:03,160 --> 01:10:04,540
My cards is on the table, man.

933
01:10:04,550 --> 01:10:06,010
It got done. didn't it?

934
01:10:11,710 --> 01:10:14,650
Damn. That is just ...

935
01:10:14,670 --> 01:10:17,150
A mean lady.

936
01:10:17,230 --> 01:10:18,630
Yeah. You get used to it.

937
01:10:20,600 --> 01:10:22,920
And I'm the bad guy?

938
01:10:26,590 --> 01:10:27,590
That's gangsta.

939
01:10:29,590 --> 01:10:30,490
What?

940
01:10:30,500 --> 01:10:32,200
for any of this any of it.

941
01:10:32,210 --> 01:10:35,720
I've buried a lot of mistakes, too.

942
01:10:45,820 --> 01:10:47,390
No way.

943
01:10:57,220 --> 01:10:58,220
Let's go home.

944
01:10:58,980 --> 01:11:00,180
Yeah. let's go home.

945
01:11:01,380 --> 01:11:03,830
you guys wanna go home?

946
01:11:04,690 --> 01:11:06,150
Or you wanna go back to prison?

947
01:11:06,390 --> 01:11:08,210
I'm not going back to prison.

948
01:11:08,230 --> 01:11:09,270
What I'm saying is ...

949
01:11:09,590 --> 01:11:11,910
before they kill us.

950
01:11:12,470 --> 01:11:13,470
I got this.

951
01:11:17,360 --> 01:11:19,030
You all made it this far.

952
01:11:19,880 --> 01:11:23,530
and run a good thing.

953
01:11:39,870 --> 01:11:40,870
I like her.

954
01:11:45,140 --> 01:11:45,770
Savior one- zero,

955
01:11:46,370 --> 01:11:47,450
this is Ground Element.

956
01:11:50,860 --> 01:11:53,080
how copy?

957
01:11:54,980 --> 01:11:57,510
Savior one- zero, the LZ's clear.

958
01:12:03,060 --> 01:12:04,620
Boss, they're not talking to me.

959
01:12:06,670 --> 01:12:08,010
Our bird's been jacked.

960
01:12:08,980 --> 01:12:09,980
Light it up!

961
01:12:36,700 --> 01:12:38,680
What? I got hickey or something?

962
01:12:38,680 --> 01:12:41,410
Professor, could you pick up the pace?

963
01:12:43,880 --> 01:12:45,580
Now!

964
01:12:53,060 --> 01:12:54,060
Harley!

965
01:12:57,190 --> 01:12:58,190
Hello, baby.

966
01:13:01,040 --> 01:13:02,250
Kill her!

967
01:13:03,970 --> 01:13:06,060
Her nanite's disarmed!

968
01:13:08,220 --> 01:13:09,220
Come on, baby.

969
01:13:25,030 --> 01:13:26,030
Deadshot ...

970
01:13:27,180 --> 01:13:28,980
Shoot that woman right now!

971
01:13:29,310 --> 01:13:31,150
She ain't do shit to me.

972
01:13:31,240 --> 01:13:33,340
You're a hitman. right?

973
01:13:33,480 --> 01:13:34,850
I got a contract.

974
01:13:34,920 --> 01:13:36,410
Kill Harley Quinn.

975
01:13:36,470 --> 01:13:38,740
and your kid.

976
01:13:40,580 --> 01:13:42,640
Now she dead.

977
01:14:22,060 --> 01:14:23,060
I missed.

978
01:14:28,340 --> 01:14:29,340
Good one, mate.

979
01:14:29,760 --> 01:14:31,340
It's Waller.

980
01:14:31,550 --> 01:14:35,470
Shoot it down.

981
01:14:35,470 --> 01:14:37,310
going hot.

982
01:14:45,180 --> 01:14:46,180
Puddin'!

983
01:14:51,400 --> 01:14:53,550
You got all dressed up for me?

984
01:14:53,660 --> 01:14:55,960
You know I'd do anything for you.

985
01:14:56,120 --> 01:14:56,630
By the way ...

986
01:14:56,970 --> 01:15:00,520
and a bear skin rug waitin'.

987
01:15:00,520 --> 01:15:01,520
Yeah?

988
01:15:01,870 --> 01:15:03,360
Boss, we got a problem.

989
01:15:08,830 --> 01:15:12,180
- No.

990
01:15:45,560 --> 01:15:47,870
Thank you.Now get me off this roof.

991
01:15:48,690 --> 01:15:50,310
Yes, ma'am.We are inbound.

992
01:15:53,590 --> 01:15:55,980
The Joker and Harley Quinn are no more.

993
01:16:07,280 --> 01:16:08,350
Roger.I see ya.

994
01:17:18,630 --> 01:17:20,110
Waller's down.

995
01:17:37,090 --> 01:17:40,360
We had a deal.

996
01:17:40,500 --> 01:17:42,630
Without Waller, you got nothing.

997
01:18:32,720 --> 01:18:35,270
I missed you all so much.

998
01:18:35,930 --> 01:18:38,060
We're glad you could make it.

999
01:18:52,560 --> 01:18:54,320
Hey, craziness.

1000
01:19:40,380 --> 01:19:44,160
I can finish my weapon.

1001
01:19:44,380 --> 01:19:48,310
destroy your armies.

1002
01:19:48,410 --> 01:19:50,660
Do your worst, bitch!

1003
01:20:19,030 --> 01:20:20,120
So let me guess.

1004
01:20:21,320 --> 01:20:24,400
wing of trash in the sky.

1005
01:20:28,450 --> 01:20:30,960
When does this end, Flag?

1006
01:20:57,890 --> 01:21:01,080
You tell everybody everything.

1007
01:21:01,150 --> 01:21:04,050
Or me and you are gonna go right now.

1008
01:21:10,240 --> 01:21:11,310
Three days ago,

1009
01:21:11,320 --> 01:21:14,300
a non- human entity appeared in the subway station.

1010
01:21:17,440 --> 01:21:21,290
a woman with incredibles abilities.

1011
01:21:21,500 --> 01:21:23,250
Enchantress

1012
01:21:24,210 --> 01:21:25,210
A witch.

1013
01:21:26,690 --> 01:21:28,220
See, nobody could get near this thing ...

1014
01:21:28,220 --> 01:21:30,180
but the witch could.

1015
01:21:32,210 --> 01:21:33,400
Bombs ready.

1016
01:21:33,520 --> 01:21:36,800
press the button and drop it.

1017
01:21:40,620 --> 01:21:43,530
Needless to say the whole thing was a bad idea.

1018
01:21:43,540 --> 01:21:45,050
She bolted!

1019
01:21:45,760 --> 01:21:46,760
Shit!

1020
01:21:51,240 --> 01:21:52,790
Brother help me.

1021
01:21:59,530 --> 01:22:01,130
So now you know.

1022
01:22:02,300 --> 01:22:04,390
You can just kill me right now ...

1023
01:22:04,590 --> 01:22:07,450
but I'm going to have a drink.

1024
01:22:07,500 --> 01:22:09,520
hey! Deadshot, I need your help.

1025
01:22:09,620 --> 01:22:12,320
No, sir. You need a miracle.

1026
01:23:00,640 --> 01:23:02,710
Well, we almost pulled it off ...

1027
01:23:03,100 --> 01:23:06,410
Despite what everybody thought.

1028
01:23:06,420 --> 01:23:10,410
blame us for the whole thing.

1029
01:23:10,470 --> 01:23:12,770
knowing the truth.

1030
01:23:15,040 --> 01:23:16,420
The cover-up.

1031
01:23:24,340 --> 01:23:28,010
For about two sweet seconds ...

1032
01:23:28,410 --> 01:23:29,410
I had hope.

1033
01:23:30,570 --> 01:23:31,700
You had hope huh?

1034
01:23:33,960 --> 01:23:37,010
from turning, my brother.

1035
01:23:37,510 --> 01:23:38,510
You preaching?

1036
01:23:41,040 --> 01:23:43,740
How many people you killed, man?

1037
01:23:43,840 --> 01:23:46,180
no question like that, ese.

1038
01:23:49,410 --> 01:23:51,070
No kids.

1039
01:23:54,690 --> 01:23:55,690
I do.

1040
01:24:01,580 --> 01:24:04,180
I kept it hidden most of my life, but ...

1041
01:24:05,120 --> 01:24:08,300
The older I got, the stronger I got.

1042
01:24:08,390 --> 01:24:10,380
So I started using it.

1043
01:24:11,270 --> 01:24:13,250
for business, you know

1044
01:24:13,780 --> 01:24:15,540
The more power on the street I got ...

1045
01:24:15,540 --> 01:24:16,710
The more firepower I got.

1046
01:24:16,710 --> 01:24:18,050
Like that shit went hand in hand.

1047
01:24:18,050 --> 01:24:20,340
You know? One was feeding the other.

1048
01:24:24,850 --> 01:24:26,490
Except my old lady.

1049
01:24:29,010 --> 01:24:31,260
You know, she used to pray for me.

1050
01:24:49,560 --> 01:24:52,030
Why should he take it away?

1051
01:24:52,790 --> 01:24:53,790
Hey.

1052
01:24:56,120 --> 01:24:57,130
This is our home.

1053
01:24:57,430 --> 01:24:58,950
You put that back where you found it.

1054
01:25:03,070 --> 01:25:06,830
control you know, I just ...

1055
01:25:31,740 --> 01:25:32,740
And the kids?

1056
01:25:36,250 --> 01:25:37,790
He killed them.

1057
01:25:51,380 --> 01:25:53,160
Own that shit.

1058
01:25:53,930 --> 01:25:54,930
Own it.

1059
01:25:55,100 --> 01:25:57,400
gonna happen? Huh?

1060
01:25:57,600 --> 01:25:59,520
Hey Harley, Come on.

1061
01:25:59,570 --> 01:26:01,430
What you were just ...

1062
01:26:01,610 --> 01:26:02,720
Thinking you can have a happy family ...

1063
01:26:02,780 --> 01:26:05,910
and make car payments?

1064
01:26:12,770 --> 01:26:15,170
every single time you open your mouth?

1065
01:26:25,110 --> 01:26:26,990
We all are.

1066
01:26:27,100 --> 01:26:29,540
We all are!

1067
01:26:29,560 --> 01:26:30,750
Except for him.

1068
01:26:34,220 --> 01:26:36,220
Not me, shorty.

1069
01:26:42,620 --> 01:26:45,040
Yeah, you are.

1070
01:27:03,970 --> 01:27:08,120
saying I was sleeping with her?

1071
01:27:08,980 --> 01:27:09,980
Yeah.

1072
01:27:17,580 --> 01:27:21,770
chase him all the time.

1073
01:27:24,160 --> 01:27:26,430
The only woman I ever cared about ...

1074
01:27:26,430 --> 01:27:28,910
is trapped inside that monster.

1075
01:27:29,040 --> 01:27:33,810
Everything is over.

1076
01:27:34,060 --> 01:27:35,060
Everything.

1077
01:27:54,250 --> 01:27:57,320
Your daughter writes you everyday.

1078
01:28:00,140 --> 01:28:02,060
Every single day.

1079
01:28:17,700 --> 01:28:19,630
You had these the whole time?

1080
01:28:21,130 --> 01:28:24,490
You had letters from my daughter the whole time?

1081
01:28:36,670 --> 01:28:40,250
like a chapter in the Bible.

1082
01:28:46,890 --> 01:28:49,460
is not a piece of shit.

1083
01:28:58,220 --> 01:28:59,660
I'll come.

1084
01:29:03,430 --> 01:29:04,430
What?

1085
01:29:04,940 --> 01:29:06,880
You got something better to do?

1086
01:29:06,880 --> 01:29:07,880
Come on!

1087
01:29:10,210 --> 01:29:11,210
Pussies.

1088
01:29:46,940 --> 01:29:49,330
We think that thing's a weapon.

1089
01:29:49,380 --> 01:29:50,380
Here. Lower.

1090
01:29:58,110 --> 01:30:00,050
We gotta take out the big one.

1091
01:30:02,720 --> 01:30:06,490
down there in that subway.

1092
01:30:08,790 --> 01:30:10,560
Leads right underneath that building.

1093
01:30:10,720 --> 01:30:15,260
swim underneath that things feet.

1094
01:30:15,270 --> 01:30:18,530
the hell out of that son of a bitch.

1095
01:30:18,530 --> 01:30:20,010
So the swimmers can blow the bomb.

1096
01:30:37,700 --> 01:30:38,700
We got this.

1097
01:30:44,710 --> 01:30:47,150
I live underground.

1098
01:31:07,490 --> 01:31:10,550
My dear husband if I die in battle.

1099
01:31:11,180 --> 01:31:14,110
We will be together.

1100
01:31:14,770 --> 01:31:17,750
used that sword.

1101
01:31:18,740 --> 01:31:21,160
His souls trapped inside of it.

1102
01:31:21,490 --> 01:31:23,340
She talks to him.

1103
01:31:23,970 --> 01:31:24,970
Hey. well ...

1104
01:31:25,500 --> 01:31:28,200
about the crazy ones.

1105
01:31:29,420 --> 01:31:30,420
Huh?

1106
01:32:22,070 --> 01:32:23,670
You gonna fight with us?

1107
01:32:24,450 --> 01:32:25,980
What if I lose control?

1108
01:32:41,190 --> 01:32:42,190
Duck in.

1109
01:32:54,650 --> 01:32:58,380
all this trippy magic stuff right?

1110
01:32:58,800 --> 01:32:59,800
Yeah why?

1111
01:33:06,250 --> 01:33:06,930
Yeah.

1112
01:33:06,930 --> 01:33:09,600
Well, you need to handle this shit, alll right?

1113
01:33:09,160 --> 01:33:11,680
Get up there, smack on her ass,

1114
01:33:11,790 --> 01:33:13,340
tell her : " knock this shit off".

1115
01:33:17,850 --> 01:33:20,530
My boys will detonate the bomb underneath him.

1116
01:33:24,410 --> 01:33:27,460
get a drink sometimes.

1117
01:33:32,190 --> 01:33:33,790
Step out of the shadows.

1118
01:33:40,160 --> 01:33:41,760
What the hell? Grab her.

1119
01:33:43,750 --> 01:33:46,010
Why are you here?

1120
01:33:46,040 --> 01:33:49,040
Because the soldier led you?

1121
01:33:49,160 --> 01:33:50,960
And all for Waller?

1122
01:33:51,070 --> 01:33:54,100
Why do you serve those who cage you?

1123
01:33:54,160 --> 01:33:55,160
I am your ally.

1124
01:33:56,520 --> 01:33:59,290
And I know what you want.

1125
01:33:59,390 --> 01:34:02,420
Exactly what you want.

1126
01:34:43,890 --> 01:34:44,890
Baby. Baby.

1127
01:35:04,870 --> 01:35:05,870
Miss me?

1128
01:35:13,050 --> 01:35:16,910
and then we can kick in?

1129
01:35:18,110 --> 01:35:19,600
Yeah?

1130
01:35:25,320 --> 01:35:27,760
He married me.

1131
01:35:30,560 --> 01:35:32,330
I killed the Bat.

1132
01:35:34,080 --> 01:35:35,940
What? I want that.

1133
01:35:44,070 --> 01:35:47,080
How long have you been able to see?

1134
01:35:47,370 --> 01:35:49,120
My whole life.

1135
01:35:52,060 --> 01:35:53,610
These are my people right here.

1136
01:35:53,630 --> 01:35:55,510
But it is our time.

1137
01:35:55,620 --> 01:35:58,450
The sun is setting and the magic rises.

1138
01:35:58,330 --> 01:36:00,730
The met humans are a sign of change.

1139
01:36:01,730 --> 01:36:02,730
Lady ...

1140
01:36:02,770 --> 01:36:05,610
You are EVIL!

1141
01:36:06,280 --> 01:36:07,280
Brother.

1142
01:36:07,970 --> 01:36:09,300
make them bow to me.

1143
01:36:10,220 --> 01:36:11,220
Oh wow!

1144
01:36:14,680 --> 01:36:15,680
Uh-oh!

1145
01:36:16,430 --> 01:36:17,430
Who's this?

1146
01:36:19,430 --> 01:36:20,910
We should run.

1147
01:36:45,860 --> 01:36:47,930
I'll do it! I'll get him there.

1148
01:37:01,630 --> 01:37:03,670
I ain't gonaa lose one another.

1149
01:37:03,670 --> 01:37:04,900
Look, think it through ...

1150
01:37:05,110 --> 01:37:06,110
I got this.

1151
01:37:06,590 --> 01:37:08,790
Let me show you what I really am.

1152
01:37:10,390 --> 01:37:11,390
Over here!

1153
01:37:54,030 --> 01:37:55,030
Go!

1154
01:38:09,080 --> 01:38:10,930
Rick, in position. Standing by.

1155
01:38:11,150 --> 01:38:13,050
Diablo, drive him into the corner!

1156
01:38:27,570 --> 01:38:29,300
- Come on.

1157
01:38:30,650 --> 01:38:32,260
Yeah, do it.

1158
01:38:42,180 --> 01:38:44,420
Get out of there!

1159
01:38:44,500 --> 01:38:45,960
Blow it!

1160
01:38:48,910 --> 01:38:50,280
Blow it.

1161
01:38:52,640 --> 01:38:53,640
Now GQ, now.

1162
01:38:53,980 --> 01:38:54,980
NO!

1163
01:38:56,770 --> 01:38:57,770
Everybody down!

1164
01:39:06,830 --> 01:39:09,710
Brother!

1165
01:39:35,930 --> 01:39:36,930
You next.

1166
01:39:38,870 --> 01:39:41,860
My spell is complete.

1167
01:39:41,990 --> 01:39:45,830
my darkness will spread across this world.

1168
01:39:45,900 --> 01:39:49,710
And it would be mine to rule.

1169
01:40:04,610 --> 01:40:06,810
That was our main satellite uplink.

1170
01:40:11,550 --> 01:40:13,620
How did this witch even know how to target this thing?

1171
01:40:20,130 --> 01:40:21,860
You got a move here, Flag?

1172
01:40:21,990 --> 01:40:24,390
We gotta cut her heart out.

1173
01:40:56,450 --> 01:40:59,190
that thing is laying waste to the whole damn world.

1174
01:41:06,300 --> 01:41:07,300
Where is she?

1175
01:41:13,710 --> 01:41:14,710
Hey.

1176
01:41:21,350 --> 01:41:22,710
Look out look out!

1177
01:41:46,960 --> 01:41:47,960
Sorry.

1178
01:41:53,810 --> 01:41:54,810
Flag!

1179
01:42:29,410 --> 01:42:31,080
Enough!

1180
01:42:34,320 --> 01:42:36,870
Of all who have faced me ...

1181
01:42:36,940 --> 01:42:39,710
you have earned mercy.

1182
01:42:39,790 --> 01:42:42,270
For the last time ...

1183
01:42:42,370 --> 01:42:44,180
join me ...

1184
01:42:44,290 --> 01:42:46,020
or die.

1185
01:42:51,670 --> 01:42:54,020
but maybe we should.

1186
01:42:54,140 --> 01:42:55,610
Hey.

1187
01:42:57,340 --> 01:42:58,340
So?

1188
01:42:58,980 --> 01:43:01,260
done for us anyway?

1189
01:43:01,380 --> 01:43:02,610
It hates us.

1190
01:43:03,160 --> 01:43:05,210
Hey Harley!

1191
01:43:08,190 --> 01:43:10,050
Hey lady?

1192
01:43:12,530 --> 01:43:14,830
I lost my Puddin'.

1193
01:43:16,000 --> 01:43:18,270
But you can get him back, right?

1194
01:43:18,920 --> 01:43:21,150
I can, my dear.

1195
01:43:21,450 --> 01:43:24,520
Anything you want.

1196
01:43:27,210 --> 01:43:28,070
You promise?

1197
01:43:28,080 --> 01:43:30,220
Yes. child.

1198
01:43:31,840 --> 01:43:33,640
you need only Bow ...

1199
01:43:34,610 --> 01:43:38,590
and serve beneath my feet.

1200
01:43:51,150 --> 01:43:52,920
You messed with my friends.

1201
01:43:58,380 --> 01:44:00,710
We can ends this.

1202
01:44:05,130 --> 01:44:06,130
Hey, Croc!

1203
01:44:09,760 --> 01:44:11,190
Harley!

1204
01:45:03,950 --> 01:45:05,690
Daddy I love you.

1205
01:46:03,280 --> 01:46:04,700
That was a great shot man.

1206
01:46:16,390 --> 01:46:19,090
Let me join my brother.

1207
01:46:20,000 --> 01:46:21,000
Katana, no!

1208
01:46:26,350 --> 01:46:27,350
Give me that.

1209
01:46:29,480 --> 01:46:30,820
you bring June back.

1210
01:46:31,050 --> 01:46:32,190
you bring her back.

1211
01:46:32,320 --> 01:46:34,450
She's not coming back.

1212
01:46:34,680 --> 01:46:35,580
I'll crush this.

1213
01:46:35,710 --> 01:46:37,170
Do you hear me?

1214
01:46:37,310 --> 01:46:39,000
You bring June back or I'll crush this!

1215
01:46:39,160 --> 01:46:40,870
Go ahead.

1216
01:46:41,420 --> 01:46:43,630
You don't have the balls.

1217
01:47:36,210 --> 01:47:37,710
Hey, Flag.

1218
01:47:47,220 --> 01:47:48,220
June!

1219
01:47:57,580 --> 01:47:59,360
She's gone.

1220
01:47:59,410 --> 01:48:01,000
I though killed you.

1221
01:48:01,160 --> 01:48:02,890
I thought I killed you.

1222
01:48:03,890 --> 01:48:09,190
I got me a sewer to crawl back into.

1223
01:48:09,310 --> 01:48:11,760
to handle back in Gotham.

1224
01:48:11,880 --> 01:48:13,330
Need a ride?

1225
01:48:13,360 --> 01:48:14,700
you are not driving.

1226
01:48:14,800 --> 01:48:15,800
Why not?

1227
01:48:18,680 --> 01:48:20,900
How are you not dead?

1228
01:48:21,290 --> 01:48:23,430
We just saved the world.

1229
01:48:23,950 --> 01:48:25,910
A "thank you" would be nice.

1230
01:48:26,250 --> 01:48:27,730
Thank you.

1231
01:48:28,300 --> 01:48:29,300
You're welcome.

1232
01:48:29,510 --> 01:48:31,510
and we don't get shit?

1233
01:48:31,760 --> 01:48:34,330
Ten years off you prison sentences.

1234
01:48:37,210 --> 01:48:40,440
I'm seeing my daughter.

1235
01:48:42,650 --> 01:48:44,150
That can be arranged.

1236
01:48:45,200 --> 01:48:46,960
Ant other requests?

1237
01:48:47,590 --> 01:48:49,460
An espresso machine.

1238
01:48:49,820 --> 01:48:51,700
BET.

1239
01:48:52,080 --> 01:48:54,970
Ten years off a triple life sentence?

1240
01:48:54,980 --> 01:48:56,880
a free man. .

1241
01:48:56,880 --> 01:48:58,890
Or we're to start having some real fun.

1242
01:48:58,890 --> 01:49:02,030
Why don't have some fun?

1243
01:49:10,530 --> 01:49:13,740
You're trying to figure out this length.

1244
01:49:14,230 --> 01:49:15,590
That's the hypotenuse.

1245
01:49:16,030 --> 01:49:17,430
So you have to know this angle.

1246
01:49:17,670 --> 01:49:20,360
Okay. So, if you're up here ...

1247
01:49:20,380 --> 01:49:21,800
like an a building ...

1248
01:49:21,950 --> 01:49:25,230
an the street ...

1249
01:49:25,280 --> 01:49:27,580
That's how far the bullet actually goes?

1250
01:49:28,210 --> 01:49:30,300
Yeah. That's ... that's right!

1251
01:49:30,510 --> 01:49:31,950
Tou are so smart, Right.

1252
01:49:31,950 --> 01:49:34,250
the hypotenuse, good one.

1253
01:49:35,370 --> 01:49:37,290
have to know the angle ...

1254
01:49:37,400 --> 01:49:39,820
Between the building and the sidewalk.

1255
01:49:39,830 --> 01:49:41,550
You got to know that angle.

1256
01:49:41,560 --> 01:49:43,210
No, I mean, in real life ...

1257
01:49:43,210 --> 01:49:44,260
You have variables.

1258
01:49:44,330 --> 01:49:45,810
you know. you got rifling twist.

1259
01:49:45,810 --> 01:49:48,430
You got bullet weight.

1260
01:49:48,980 --> 01:49:52,940
the curvature of the earth in with the ...

1261
01:49:53,070 --> 01:49:54,480
It's time.

1262
01:49:55,750 --> 01:49:56,750
... Wind effect.

1263
01:49:58,540 --> 01:50:00,800
You know, there's a lot variables ...

1264
01:50:01,670 --> 01:50:03,370
In the street.

1265
01:50:06,910 --> 01:50:08,420
I gotta go.

1266
01:50:08,990 --> 01:50:10,320
Are you coming back?

1267
01:50:12,220 --> 01:50:13,220
Yeah.

1268
01:50:13,320 --> 01:50:15,950
I'm working it out. All right?

1269
01:50:15,950 --> 01:50:20,810
that i would just, you know, go ...

1270
01:50:20,820 --> 01:50:22,750
Without  killing them all.

1271
01:50:22,830 --> 01:50:24,010
Bring in it.

1272
01:50:27,130 --> 01:50:28,260
I love you. Daddy.

1273
01:50:31,120 --> 01:50:32,600
I love you.

1274
01:50:58,290 --> 01:51:01,080
Hey! Let me out!

1275
01:51:01,080 --> 01:51:03,000
Let me out of here right now!

1276
01:51:03,310 --> 01:51:06,480
Hey! you feel that? yeah.

1277
01:51:06,760 --> 01:51:10,400
please, I'm begging you. Seriously.

1278
01:51:10,400 --> 01:51:13,730
Because I'm a brilliant driver.

1279
01:51:13,840 --> 01:51:15,650
Come on!

1280
01:52:09,910 --> 01:52:11,750
Puddin''!

1281
01:52:13,880 --> 01:52:16,300
Let's go home.

1282
01:52:29,920 --> 01:52:34,750
What do you want?

1283
01:52:34,750 --> 01:52:35,830
People have asked questions

1284
01:52:35,870 --> 01:52:37,240
about Midway City.

1285
01:52:37,370 --> 01:52:38,900
The kind of people can get the answers,

1286
01:52:39,100 --> 01:52:42,090
And if they can get those answers, [???]

1287
01:52:42,390 --> 01:52:46,300
Consider yourself under my protection. If you deliver.

1288
01:53:02,860 --> 01:53:03,990
Why, Mr. Wayne?

1289
01:53:06,660 --> 01:53:07,970
It likes to make friends.

1290
01:53:10,020 --> 01:53:11,020
It's the difference between us

1291
01:53:11,060 --> 01:53:12,060
You believe in friendship.

1292
01:53:12,170 --> 01:53:13,250
I believe in the leverage.

1293
01:53:14,790 --> 01:53:15,790
Goodnight.

1294
01:53:15,910 --> 01:53:17,270
You look tired.

1295
01:53:17,860 --> 01:53:20,110
You should stop working at nights.

1296
01:53:21,070 --> 01:53:24,960
or my friends and I will for you.

1297
00:38:34,400 --> 00:38:35,430
01:00:28:018

1298
01:48:49,040 --> 01:48:51,340
BET

