BIRD CAWS
He's a magician.
No, he smells too nice.
BIRD CAWS
Morning.
HORSE NEIGHS
Your book, sir.
I'm obliged to you.
'Some years ago, there
was, in the city of York,
'a society of magicians.
'They met up on the third Wednesday
of every month and read
'each other long, dull papers upon
'the history of English magic.
'They were gentlemen
magicians, which is
'to say they had never
harmed anyone by magic.
'Nor ever done anyone
the slightest good.
'In fact, to own the truth,
'not one of these magicians had
ever cast the smallest spell.
'Nor, by magic, caused one leaf to
tremble upon a tree, made one mote
'of dust alter its course
or changed a single
'hair upon anyone's head.
'With this one minor reservation,
'they enjoyed a reputation as some
'of the wisest and
most magical gentlemen
'in Yorkshire.'
Mr...
Mr Segundus!
~ Yes.
~ HE COUGHS
Excuse me. Er...
ha...
It has been no small inducement,
in my coming to York,
that your excellent and, er,
distinguished society exists here.
~ Er, not to mention your extensive
library of magical books.
~ That's right.
Er, I have studied magic,
gentlemen, for many years.
The histories of the Raven King,
the great magicians of long ago.
I've read the new publications
and even made my small
contribution to their number.
~ HE COUGHS
~ Excuse me.
But I... but I have recently
begun to wonder why the great
feats of magic that I read about
remain in the pages of my books...
and are not seen on the street or...
on the battlefield.
I have begun to wonder why modern
magicians are unable to work
the magic that they write about.
In short, gentlemen,
I wish to know...
.. why is magic no longer
done in England.
THEY ALL MUTTER
It is a long question, Mr...
Segundus.
Magicians study magic,
the history of magic.
We do not perform it.
You don't expect an astronomer
to create stars, eh?
THEY ALL CHUCKLE
Or a botanist to invent
new flowers, eh?
~ THEY ALL LAUGH
~ It is a child's question, I
appreciate, but no-one else...
Classical magic, sir, is not a thing
for the gentlemen of this society.
Nor any...
gentleman.
I do hope that you have not been
trying to cast spells, sir.
THEY ALL LAUGH
You told me certainly that there
would be books coming in.
You took a guinea from me.
Good day to you, sir.
Mr Segundus, I say.
Honeyfoot. I was there at the
society last night. May I?
I have made myself disagreeable.
No, sir. I think you hit
upon it quite correct.
Why is magic no longer done?
I cannot find it answered anywhere.
Can you believe there are
no books of magic to be had?
In York!
~ Books about magic are rare enough.
~ Books of magic.
Oh, my dear fellow, they're
more precious than rubies.
Even the society only
has a few pages.
I have tried everywhere else.
The society is my last
throw of the dice. Sir!
We're growing stale,
we need fresh opinions.
Oh, I'm... I'm afraid that those
books have been sold, sir.
I reserved them!
Yes, I am sorry for it, sir.
Oh, it is no matter.
Do you have anything upon the nature
of clouds, rain, atmospheres?
Yes, sir. Yes, I do,
as a matter of fact.
Oh, that's interesting. I'm most
fascinated by clouds myself.
Keep an eye open.
Mr Segundus.
At least I can find the devil
who keeps swiping my books.
Ah.
There.
Norrell.
Hurtfew Abbey.
It is not an age for magic.
Why then do you persist, sir?
What is it?
Tremendously dirty.
From a street magician in London.
"A spell to join together articles
"which have been parted."
~ Does it work?
~ No.
He was a vagabond, you see.
Yellow curtain sort of fellow.
Persuaded me to part with a rather
large sum of money for that.
And then he called me back, said
he'd tell me a secret for nothing.
Told me that one day magic would
be restored to England by
two magicians.
Old prophecies are nonsense.
I know.
But it set me upon my present path.
We are two magicians. John
Segundus and Mr Honeyfoot.
Sounds well.
One would expect him to pretend
that I was one of the two,
but in the end he told me, rather
plainly, that I was not.
Mr Norrell?
Come in.
Watch your step,
gentlemen. The way is...
convoluted.
HE COUGHS
It's Mr Honeyfoot and Mr Segundus
of the York Society of Magicians.
I read your account of the careers
of Martin Pale's fairy servants, sir.
It's a creditable piece of work.
Well...
there was Master
Fallowthought, was there not?
You left him out.
A minor spirit, but nevertheless...
Fallowthought?
I have never even heard of him.
Forgive me, sir, but what a library!
Yes, I forget. Of course,
he is described in
Holgarth and Pickles' history of their
own dealings with Master Fallowthought,
which you can scarcely have read.
You have that book?
May we, may we be permitted to...
Nothing would be more
agreeable to me.
How To Putte Questions To The
Dark And Understand Its Answers.
It's a foolish work.
This is Belasis's instructions.
Every copy of this was
destroyed centuries ago.
I did devote a great deal of time to
Belasis in my youth, but no longer.
He is mystical when he
should be clear and clear
when he should be mystical.
These are all... books of magic.
Mr Norrell, such...
~ Surely you will find your answer here.
~ Answer?
To a simple question, sir.
In the past, magic was done
as a matter of course.
It... it was as much a part
of this country as the rain.
Then 300 years ago it died,
seemingly overnight.
We wish to know...
why magic has fallen from
its once great state.
We wish to know why is there
no more magic done in England?
It is a wrong question, sir.
Magic is not ended in England.
I myself am quite a tolerable,
practical...
magician.
Well done.
Well... it is done.
Show these gentlemen
out, Childermass.
~ LAUGHTER
~ Absolute tripe!
Oh, I'm so sorry, sirs,
to see you bringing magic
into such disrepute.
This Norrell is lying.
I disa... I disagree,
I believe Mr Norrell.
Did you see magic
done or did you not?
THEY ALL STIR
Gentlemen, the answer
is a simple one, eh?
We shall invite Mr Norrell to
prove his ridiculous assertion.
To do magic for us.
And if he cannot, or will not,
to lay off disturbing
our peace of mind!
THEY ALL CHEER
This is the hour and place he
appointed, and he doesn't come.
Mr Norrell concedes defeat.
Not at all.
Who are you, sir?
A word or two before you go in.
If Mr Norrell fails to do
the magic he has promised,
he will publicly withdraw his claim
to be a practical magician,
~ indeed a magician of any sort.
~ That's quite right.
And swears never to make
any such claim again.
~ Here's his hand on it.
~ I'm sure he needn't go so far.
We have no desire to punish him.
However, my master only thinks
it's fair to extract the same
promise from each of you...
.. should he succeed.
Here's the paper and there's
the stuff to sign your name.
Well, I do not believe
he can do magic,
and so...
I will sign because I believe he can.
And I hope he achieves recognition
and will use his powers for the good
of the nation in this time of war.
Sir.
I will not sign. Magic
is my life, sir.
What shall I do when
it is taken from me?
We shall say Mr Norrell's
contract is with all
members of the society...
.. except Mr Segundus.
BELL CHIMES
HE CHUCKLES
RUMBLING
WIND BLOWS
WHISPERING: 'Come here. Come here.
'Come here.'
~ WHISPERING:
~ 'We saw him.
~ Tyranny. Tyranny.
~ 'He murdered her.
~ He murdered her.
~ 'We know. We know. We saw him.
~ We saw it.
'There was no-one to
see but the stones.
~ 'No-one saw but the stones.
~ The stones, the stones.
'He murdered her! And no-one saw!'
The statues.
'The stones. Dig up his bones!
'Let him be punished
for his wickedness!'
He has brought them alive.
SCREAMING
Ooh!
Oh!
~ STATUES: Usurper.
~ Usurper? How dare you?!
~ Lady Catherine. Catherine of Winchester.
~ You killed my horse, sir!
Oh, forever upon that damned horse!
Get you gone, father.
My boot is on the wrong foot
and it is paining my bunion.
STATUES SING AND PLAY
HE SPEAKS IN LATIN
I don't know what you're
talking about.
HE SPEAKS IN LATIN
I don't know! HE SPEAKS IN LATIN
We have not seen the likes
of that for three centuries!
I am sorry for it, sirs.
Do not be.
Magic is restored to England.
I hope it can do some good.
Do you think Mr Norrell
would be offended
if I wrote to the London
newspapers of this?
I very much think he would be.
But I rather think my master has
hidden his talent long enough.
It is time for him to take his place.
And London is where I shall take him.
Well, if that is how the
first magician behaves,
I dare not think what
the second will be like.
'The Lord be with you.'
Let us pray.
In the desolate plateau of
the Iberian peninsula...
.. and on the battlefields of
France and the low countries.
Lord, we beseech your help in
these times for our country.
Fighting a Godless enemy.
Lord, we ask for courage, wisdom.
For the support of your
grace and the endurance
of your providence.
Which daily strengthens us. Amen.
ALL: Amen.
'Well done, Henry.'
You're using your voice much
better, more authority.
Yes, I... I think you have
definitely improved.
Especially the, er, the voice.
Thank you, Jonathan.
We'd saved a place for you.
Oh, I did not see.
I was at the back.
Yes. Right at the back.
Enjoying your Sunday, Mr Atkinson?
I... I've done everything
you want in the way of...
I hardly play cards.
I drink very, very little, scarcely
more than a bottle a day.
And, well...
I've no objection to going
to church more often.
Twice a week if you'd like it better.
I leave such matters
to your own conscience.
I do not know, perhaps you don't
like my going to Bath or Brighton
or...
But really, the ladies there, you
have nothing to fear from them.
They are without doubt
very charming, but...
That hadn't even occurred to me.
Oh.
~ Arabella.
~ Jonathan.
I only wish that you would...
find a way to occupy your time.
No-one loves a holiday better than
I, but perpetual holidays...
~ Does it make you happy?
~ You make me happy.
~ A man needs an occupation, Jonathan.
~ Arabella, you know perfectly
well that my father...
~ I'm going away.
~ What?
With Henry, to his new
parish. Help him settle.
Oh.
I'd not thought to do this
now, but I see I must act.
Jonathan?
Do not act.
Think.
I'll not be gone forever.
'It is cruel, sir,'
for a fellow of my age to be
kept from taking up any useful
position in the world.
It is no wonder that I go to
seed in this manner of which
you so desperately disapprove.
Which useful position
had you in mind?
Any, sir. Give it to
me and I shall fill it.
HE SNEEZES
One more of those and you'll
lose YOUR position, sir.
As for you, let me see, you have...
HE SNEEZES Good God, man!
For pity's sake, Father.
Have him close the window,
the man is clearly ill.
Open all the windows.
I'm not blind, my son.
This clergyman's girl wishes
you to be a man of destiny.
She does not know that you,
like your mother, are weak
and skittish and doomed to fulfil no
function more useful than
that of a clothes horse.
HE GROANS
~ My dear fellow!
~ Leave him!
On your feet, sir.
Stand beside the window.
And you, sir, you've proved yourself
a failure in everything you've done.
And you shall have no assistance
in finding any occupation whilst
I am yet living and
master in this house.
I had thought to ask your
permission to marry your sister.
But I rather think it is her
permission I'd struggle to get.
Have some brandy in that, Henry.
It makes it taste much better.
It is Sunday, Jonathan. I
have a carriage to catch.
Arabella loves you. She merely...
~ I have tried.
~ She just wishes you to have purpose.
I have tried to buy an ironworks,
the smelting room gave me a headache.
I have tried to establish a business
to collect fossils at Lyme Regis.
~ Yes.
~ Much too rainy. Have you,
have you been to Lyme Regis?
Cannot your father...
My father delights in torturing
me, as he tortures his servants.
As he tortured my mother.
Jonathan, God will...
A way will become clear
to you, Jonathan.
All I've ever truly wished
for is your sister.
It often happens in the
most unexpected of ways.
Goodbye, Jonathan.
Do not drown yourself.
I will have one more.
KNOCKING ON DOOR
HE STIRS
~ What?
~ I fear there's been a quarrel.
The door, it's quite jammed.
Come on, together.
The poor fellow is ill!
HE GROANS
This room is as cold
as a Scotsman's chimney!
Father!
Father?
BELL TOLLS
She regrets her absence
in Cumberland.
She does not like to
think of me being alone
and friendless at such a time.
Well, I have an estate to run.
I'm not to be without
an occupation now.
~ What sort of an interval
do you think is appropriate?
~ Eh?
For me to ride up there and
ask for her hand, Jeremy.
To Cumberland!
What sort of period of mourning
do you think is fit?
A month? Two weeks?
Three days?
BELL RINGS
"And Mr Norrell, having taken a
London house for the season..."
I have not taken it,
I have bought it.
210 guineas.
".. having taken a London house for
the season, leaves us hungry to see
"which, if any, new wonders
he will perform
"after the miracle of York."
Miracle?
"The miracle of York."
"Are we to see the proof of
his genius with our own eyes?
"Has magic truly returned,
or is Mr Norrell
"simply a wealthier version
of the familiar conjuror
~ "in his yellow-curtained tent?"
~ I have never...
I have contended with
this for 40 years.
Stiggers and disapproval.
Well, this is why we have
come here, is it not?
We have come to change that.
The Star has reprinted
Mr Segundus's letter...
with illustrations.
Why is London so expensive?
So noisy?
And the smell.
Is that supposed to be me?
With a beard?
And a pointy hat!
They intend no disrespect, sir.
That is what most folk believe
a magician to look like.
The magic of the old country.
The magic of the Raven King,
300 years gone...
and turned to feathers.
The Raven King.
These men give the practice of
magic such an appalling name.
Well, if nothing else, sir,
you should pull that picture
out of their heads.
Whoa!
Listen.
This is what you have worked for.
This is your great opportunity.
If all goes as it should here,
when folk think of a magician...
They will think of myself.
Courage, sir. Charm.
He is the Secretary of State for War.
Remember what a gift
it is that you offer,
then I am sure he
will be your friend.
'You, sir, are an
embarrassment to your party'
and to this whole house.
THEY CHEER
Our forces are hopelessly
outnumbered by the French.
We stay in Salamanca and be
massacred, or lead our troops
over the mountains and
leave them to the snow.
This is a final disgrace.
The final act of a criminally
incompetent government.
Shame upon you. Shame!
THEY ALL SHOUT
Order. Sir Walter Pole.
The honourable gentleman is
well known for his excellent
impromptu speeches, and it is
good to know that the time he
~ spends preparing them is not wasted.
~ LAUGHTER
I would have been happy
to hear a deal less of it.
But as Napoleon himself has said,
you should never interrupt your
enemy when he is making a mistake.
'There will be no retreat
from Salamanca.
But I am a man of my word and
a custodian of English blood.
There will be no retreat!
CHEERING
There will be a massacre.
MAN: Well done, Sir
Walter. Well done.
Sir Walter!
Sir Walt...
What assistance may I be to you, sir?
I have an appointment with
Sir Walter to talk about...
.. magic.
Ah, you are the magician. Mr Norris?
Norrell.
Sir Walter begs humbly that he
may receive you at his private
residence.
DOOR OPENS
Aha, I'm very glad to meet you, sir.
It seems London talks of little else
but the extraordinary Mr Norrell.
Please. Mr Norrell
is a magician, ma'am.
A person of great reputation in
his native county of Yorkshire.
And where are your
fairy servants, sir?
Are they visible only to yourself
or may others see them?
Oh, uh, fairies are
mythological creatures, madam.
Mythological?
I meant to say that they do no...
They... they did not exist in
the way the stories have them.
They're a poisonous race, their
help is always regretted, it is
always a heavy price.
You are not at all what
I expected, eh, Stephen?
I had not formed a picture
of Mr Norrell, sir.
I had heard you were
a practical magician.
I hope you are not offended.
It's a great relief to see that
you are nothing of the sort.
You are a theoretical
magician, I imagine.
SHE COUGHS
They say you have
something to ask me?
SHE COUGHS
I...
W... That is
to say, I beg your pardon but
I am in fact a practical,
erm, magician.
But I very earnestly hope that
I will not by this admission
lose your good opinion.
No, by no means.
The... the misapprehension
under which you labour...
by which I mean of course the
belief that all practical
magicians are charlatans,
arises from the appalling
idleness of English magicians
in the last 300 years.
I have performed one small
feat of modern magic, which
the people of York were kind enough
to say that they found astounding.
I am come, Sir Walter, to offer you
my help in our present difficulties.
~ You mean the war?
~ Yes.
My dear sir, what has magic
to do with the war?
I believe I have heard
what you did in York
and I am sure the housewives
were very grateful.
But I can scarcely see how such
magic may be applied to the war.
True enough, soldiers get very dirty.
Sir, I made half-a-hundred stone
figures talk in York Minster.
It was nothing to do with housewives.
COUGHING
My fiancee, Miss Wintertowne.
Oh, er, enchante, miss.
Very fond of magic myself.
There's a wonderful street
magician - Vinculus.
~ He's all lies and doom.
~ Oh, well, no, street magicians
are the very worst.
All magicians are vagabonds.
My dear Emma is to be
married to Sir Walter
at St George's in ten days' time.
M... many congratulations.
SHE COUGHS
I am often ill myself.
I find some warm lemon and nutmeg...
SHE COUGHS
Mr Norrell, I'm not sure what
help you hope to offer us.
I am sorry to say it will not do.
Magic is not respectable, sir.
The government cannot
meddle in such things.
Frankly, had I better understood
what you were proposing to offer,
I would not have agreed to meet you.
CLOCK CHIMES
~ How'd it go?
~ Very well.
Tolerably well.
As bad as that, eh? Did
you do any magic for him?
This is not the way to the house.
Hanover Square is that way.
We are going to Lady Godesdone's
house. It's a soiree.
A party? I wish to go
home and read a book.
Powerful gentlemen spend
more time at parties
than they do in Parliament.
You cannot do this from the comfort
of your own fireside, sir.
We're not in Yorkshire any more.
CHATTER AND LAUGHTER
Pardon me. Excuse me.
I heard all the ladies of Yorkshire
may put out their dirty linen
in baskets at night, and in the
morning it is magically clean.
He is as rich as a very Jew.
A wealthy uncle died, leaving him
a large estate, Hurtfew Abbey.
~ It's in Yorkshire.
~ Wealthy uncles are in
short supply these days.
I was with him, only this morning, to hear
of the wonderful magic he's been doing.
What kind of wonderful magic
are we talking about, exactly?
The cleaning of laundry
is commonly known.
LAUGHTER AND CHATTER
HE BREATHES HEAVILY
Admit it, you don't know him.
On the contrary, nobody in
London knows him better.
We came here in the expectation of
seeing something very extraordinary,
such as we have read in the Times,
and instead we have been forced
to make our own entertainment.
That gentleman is reading a book!
I beg your pardon.
No, no, you do not know him as I.
Mr Norrell has a shrewd
notion of his own value.
A gentleman who buys a
house in Hanover Square.
~ I beg your pardon.
~ What!
I am Mr Norrell.
Oh!
Mr Norrell!
I can scarcely begin to express my
delight in making your acquaintance.
I had mistook you, sir.
But now that I behold you, I plainly
see you have the measured
and dignified air of
a magical scholar.
Lascelles, do you not think
Mr Norrell has the grave
and sober bearing of a scholar?
~ 'Spose so.
~ My name is Drawlight.
I have been your John the Baptist,
sir, preparing the way for you.
I knew we would be friends.
Here we are, chatting so
comfortably to one another.
This is all for you, sir.
Yes, I am becoming aware of that.
Let me announce you.
And I pray, do not think it
would be considered an insult
to the company if you were to
perform a trick or two of magic.
No, no, no, no... I...
GLASS TINKLES
My lords.
My, my lords, ladies and gentlemen,
may I introduce to
you my dear friend,
the saviour of English magic,
the magician of Hanover
Square, Mr Norrell.
He has disappeared.
DISHES CLATTER
Can I help you, sir?
The rain shall make a door for me.
And I shall walk through it.
Oh, yes, you think yourself
a very fine fellow.
Hoarding books like
a miser hoards gold.
Open up!
Well, I have a book, sir.
A book you won't find in
your library, or any other.
It's written by the Raven King,
and it tells me all about you.
Vinculus, magician of Threadneedle
Street, at your service.
Well, know this, magician -
your coming was foretold long ago.
I've been expecting you
these past 20 years.
Now I've come to explain
your destiny to you,
as it is written in my book.
Oh, prophecies, is it!
Well, magic cannot
see into the future
and rascals who claim
otherwise are liars.
~ Childermass!
~ These are the words of the Raven King.
He was a charlatan, sir. Childermass!
~ Two magicians shall appear in England.
~ Two?
The name of one shall be Fearfulness,
the name of the other, Arrogance.
~ Did you say two?
~ Ssh.
The first shall fear me, the
second shall long to behold me.
The first shall bury his heart
in the dark wood beneath the snow,
yet still feel its ache.
The second shall see his dearest
possession in his enemy's hand.
Both will fail.
The nameless slave shall
be a king in a strange land.
I will return.
His words, sir, not mine.
I will return. There.
Goodbye.
HE SPITS
Childermass!
I want that man gone.
I want him run out of London.
You shall have some spells.
~ I don't need any spells. What did he want?
~ What?
The man put himself to a great deal of trouble
and risked a hanging. What did he want?
~ To give a prophecy from
the Raven King. Nonsense.
~ The Raven King?
He said he had a book. Nonsense.
But if he does have a book, I want it,
and then I want to go home to Yorkshire.
To Yorkshire? We've
only just moved here.
This house is not respectable
enough - such a tiny library.
No, you're doing it wrong. You've got dozens
of invitations to fancy houses and you,
you either turn them
down or you scarper.
That's not how you get things done.
Why do you not at least do some
magic here? Just show them.
I'm not a performing monkey.
Have Davy bring down
the packing boxes.
Do you wish to make a success
of this? Or do you not?
There.
Take these spells.
Use them if you must.
One-penny spells, two-penny spells.
I got a guinea spell for you, sir.
Let me importune some fortune into
your sorry little life, sir.
Pull out your purses and procure
some curses. All right, darling?
For five shillings I'll confer
with the River Thames and find
that runaway husband of yours, eh?
No? How much for your pies, mate?
More than you've got.
Ah! Mr Norrell, sir.
Drawlight, hmm? Your
John the Baptist.
A moment of your time, sir.
HE SNORES
Ah!
Ah, a spell to make an
obstinate man leave London.
One spell to discover what my
enemy is doing presently. Cheap.
Well, you can tell the magician of Hanover
Square that his spells have no effect on me.
That's because I haven't cast them yet.
There's a true magician in England now.
I know magicians and I know
magic and I say this -
all magicians lie, that one
more than most. Oh, yes.
I think you and I had better
have a chat, don't you?
Why?
You left so suddenly last night, sir,
and I had so much to say and I'm
sure we will be such friends.
Davy, you should use
some calf-skin gloves.
Do mind the spines,
Lucas, the spines.
You are not leaving, sir?
I came here to restore
magic to respectability
and to do some good for the war.
I am clearly bound to fail. These
men in government will not listen.
Sir, if you will permit
me. I know these men.
Just a spell or two would have
them embracing you like a brother.
I only ask that I be the gentleman
to introduce you to society.
Just one small piece of magic.
Like you did for the
housewives in Yorkshire.
I have never washed any linen in my
life, by magical means or otherwise.
Who invented this nonsense?
I suppose it is no matter who.
So where's this book of yours?
You'll never have my book.
You'll never even see it.
~ It's my inheritance.
~ From who? The Raven King?
Well, you can't hide
the truth from me.
The cards of Marseilles.
Shall we see your fortune?
MAN: Curses! Curses
upon your neighbour!
For the present, your actions are
governed by a hermit - Norrell.
We knew that already.
Ah, this one tells me you've weighed
your choices and made a decision.
This one tells me what it
is - you're going wandering.
You've a message to deliver.
To him.
The Knight of Wands.
You may expect a meeting,
leading to an ordeal of some
sort, perhaps even death.
The cards don't say whether
or not you'll survive.
But regardless, you will
achieve your purpose.
~ Do you know what I am yet?
~ Well, there's nothing here that says
you're anything more
than a charlatan.
Then you won't mind if I tell
a fortune myself then, will you?
My fortune won't interest you.
Not yours, his.
~ Norrell's?
~ He is at a crossroads, your magician.
Let's see which path he chooses.
Shall we?
Someone's left a dirty
thumbprint on't card.
I drew these myself. There's
only one king in the pack.
Tell that to the magician
of Hanover Square.
His past, his present, his future.
He is coming, you know.
The raven is coming.
And his spell is about to be cast.
HE CACKLES
I do not wish to attend soirees,
dinner parties or salons.
I have offered my services to the
country, they have been declined.
I shall return to Yorkshire.
Good day, gentlemen.
Well, sir, you have your revenge,
~ at least as far as Walter Pole is concerned.
~ Sorry?
Sir Walter's bride
is dead. Poor thing.
A thousand pounds a
year, and quite dead.
~ She only contrived to remain
alive till the end of the week.
~ Dead?
The young lady? That
is most unexpected.
On the contrary, nothing
was more likely.
Sir Walter's need of the
money is quite desperate.
He spent a thousand pounds
on the last election alone.
It's a very dangerous thing, to
bring someone back from the dead.
It has not been done in 300 years.
No, no, I could not attempt it.
Indeed, sir, no-one proposes
that you should.
Well... No, I know the form of it.
But it is precisely the sort of
magic I've set my face against.
It relies so much upon...
Well, that is to say, the outcome,
it is quite unpredictable.
It is quite out of
the magician's power.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I shall not even think of it.
No, sir, I understand.
You have in mind a
great act of magic.
A testament to your...
extraordinary powers.
I must say I think the
idea an excellent one.
Should you succeed,
all the Poles in England
will be on your doorstep.
I have laboured all this time
to make magic - my profession -
respectable in the eyes of these
men and then still, they despise me.
Oh, my dear Mr Norrell,
such an opportunity is
unlikely to occur again.
With one stroke, you return
to us that sweet young woman
whose death no-one can hear
of without shedding a tear.
And you re-establish magic
as a power in the realm
for generations to come.
There is scarcely any form
of magic more dangerous.
It is dangerous to
the magician, and...
.. furthermore it is
dangerous to the subject.
But the subject, as
you term her, is dead.
What worse fate can befall her?
And a brave magician, surely...
I will need to send for more books.
I'll make an excellent
landowner, Jeremy.
She will tell me that I will be bored
but I shall tell her about
my plans for alms houses,
and demonstrate my concern for
the plight of the common man.
The common man over there
is attempting to violently accost
the other common man, sir.
~ Stay back!
~ YELLING
~ I don't suppose you brought
a set of pistols, did you?
~ No, sir.
Jeremy, go and fetch
me a large stick.
I say!
You! We are armed and ready.
Sh! Sir, shush.
~ What?
~ You'll wake him up.
~ Who?
~ The man. Under the hedge.
He's a magician.
If you wake a magician
before his time,
his dreams come after
you and haunt you.
He's woken up!
Don't touch him.
~ Knight of wands.
~ What did he say?
Two magicians shall
appear in England.
~ What did he say?
~ The name of one shall be Fearfulness.
The name of the other - Arrogance.
Both will fail. My
name is Vinculus, sir.
For three days now, I have
been walking westward
in search of a man destined
to become a great magician.
Due to certain mystical signs...
.. I can see that it is you.
Two magicians shall
appear in England.
The first shall fear me. The
second shall long to behold me.
The first shall be governed
by thieves and murderers.
The second shall conspire
at his own destruction.
You do not make it
sound very appealing.
Choose someone else.
~ I did not choose you, magician.
~ HE LAUGHS
You were chosen long ago.
Well, whoever did the choosing will
be disappointed. I am no magician.
Then buy these two
spells from me, sir.
They'll get you started.
I got them from a great
magician in London.
How much do you want for them?
Seven shillings and
sixpence, sir. Cough up.
All right, all right.
The nameless slave shall
be a king in a strange land.
~ Here, you! Let's have you. Workhouse.
~ That's your lot.
~ Vagrancy.
I'm not a vagrant, sir.
I have money.
Who gave him money?
~ For always and forever...
~ I think it's time we were going, Jeremy.
.. I pray remember me, upon
the moors, beneath the stars.
Good day, gentlemen.
I will return. His
words, sir, not mine.
~ HE LAUGHS
~ I will return.
When I take over the management
of my own estate...
You always told me you
hated farming, Jonathan.
Will such a thing do for you?
~ Well, I...
~ You once said
that you would rather
put out your own eyes
than spend one moment
managing the estate.
Very well, I'm going to
study magic. Will that do?
Why on earth would
you want to do that?
I met a man under a hedge who
told me I was a magician.
~ Did you indeed?
~ You do not believe me.
~ No.
On the contrary, it's all of a piece
with your usual way of doing things.
I purchased two spells from
the man under the hedge.
Would you like to see one?
~ Very dirty.
~ We magicians do not regard a little dirt.
Ancient, mysterious
spells such as these.
Second of February?
Three days ago.
Indeed.
"A spell to make an obstinate
man leave London."
"One spell to discover what mine
enemy is doing presently."
Why on earth would you want
to make people leave London?
These are horrible, Jonathan.
I require a mirror
and something dead.
Er, Jeremy, those flowers.
I think we can find you
a mirror, Jonathan.
Now, madam, an occupation.
If I make a success of this,
~ might I then presume...
~ Here we are.
Thank you. And, er, now...
The flowers must be
arranged like so...
and, er, then I draw a circle
on the mirror, like this.
And then I quarter the circle.
Jonathan, where did
you get this nonsense?
From the man under the hedge.
~ Henry, do at least try it.
~ Henry, that...
That is not your ceiling.
Who on earth is he?
And why is he your enemy?
Do you owe him money?
I do not think so.
He could be a banker, it looks
a little like the counting house.
Well, Arabella, good magicians
conjure up fairy spirits
and long-dead kings.
I appear to have summoned
the spirit of a banker.
But at least...
I AM a magician.
I wish with all my heart, Sir Walter,
that I might invite you up with
me to see what it is I do.
But the nature of this
magic demands solitude.
I will, I hope, have the honour
of showing you some magic
on another occasion.
Do not send them away, sir.
Gather as many of them around
the bed as possible.
Impress the servants.
We should have brought some Chinese
powders to throw on the fire.
Bang!
Er, I wish to go to where
Miss Wintertowne is.
This way, sir.
We will stand quietly in the corner,
sir, and afford any assistance.
~ No.
~ But, sir, we...
Gentlemen.
I have in mind to write a play
based on this sorry affair.
I shall call it...
..'Tis Pity She's A Corpse.
HE SNIGGERS
RATTLING
CREAKING
HE SCREAMS
Who in the world are you?
I am the greatest
magician of the age.
I... I am the man who is destined
to restore magic to England.
Well, obviously you are that,
or I should not be here.
But who are you?
What magic have you done?
Who was your master?
I had no master, I taught
myself... from books.
Books?
There are some rather helpful
books these days.
At least, they...
They might be helpful, when...
they're considered all together.
Should I agree to restore this
beautiful young woman to life...
.. what would be my reward?
~ What sort of thing...?
~ Oh, my wishes are the most moderate things
in the world.
I simply wish to be able to
aid you in your endeavours.
To advise you in all matters
and to guide your studies.
Oh, and you must take
care to tell the world
that your greatest achievements
are due, in large part, to me.
W... Were I the sort of magician
who entrusts his business
to other persons then I would...
But I fear, unfortunately, that
I have no notion to employ you
or indeed any other member
of your race ever again.
Well...
this is most ungrateful indeed.
Perhaps I would do better
to speak to the other one.
~ The other who?
~ The other magician.
No, there is no other magician.
I am the only one.
Of course there is another magician.
He is your dearest friend
in all the world.
I have no friends.
So you will not help me?
I must confess...
.. that in recent centuries,
I have grown somewhat tired of the
society of my cousins and servants.
I have need of new companions
and this young woman would be
a charming companion indeed.
Grant me half her life
and the deal is done.
~ What would her friends and family say...?
~ Half a life
is better than none.
How long is a life?
How long would you like?
Well, let us suppose that she might
have lived until she was...
94.
And she is 19. That's
another 75 years.
75 years, then.
Exactly half of which belongs to me.
~ Shall we sign something?
~ No.
No.
I should take something of the
lady's to signify my claim.
~ One of her rings?
~ No.
Ah... I have it.
And then you will go back.
I am sorry?
After you've finished the spell,
you will go away not
to come back any more.
You need never see me again.
SHRIEKING
Emma! Miss Wintertowne.
What are you doing, man?
Open this door!
For the love of Christ,
sir, open this door.
What have you done?
SHE GASPS AND CHOKES
Oh, my Lord, my Lord.
Emma.
You've been wicked.
It is not right you did not
tell me how poorly I was.
I do believe for a moment
I may have been dead,
though I do not seem to be
dead presently. How unusual.
And Walter, I rather like
you in black. Let us dance.
Emma...
Your finger.
I don't feel it. Mmm. Dance with me.
SHE LAUGHS
A miracle!
The magician of Hanover Square has
restored the young lady to life.
My dear friend, Mr Norrell.
He has performed that which
medicine could not.
Physicians had abandoned her.
The poor young lady... Restored
to life and to dance!